Lately, the little girl's been staring
blankly into the air a lot.
I see them.
There are lots of moving circles.
I shall catch them.
Circles...
What should I do?!
She really is becoming detached from humanity now!
Circles, circles...
"Shigaraki has adopted a cute animal
form to be more popular with girls"
Moving circles? That sounds like floaters!
Floaters?
That's the thing where you can see stuff
floating around in your eyeball, right?
In any case, you should see an optometrist.
Where did I put my insurance card?
So this is a floater, huh?
You're not seeing floaters! You're seeing spirits!
hanchahan isshohan
半チャーハン 一升半
Half fried rice! Half a bushel!
say say
シェイシェイ
Say, say!
yeah yeah
いえーいえー
Yeah, yeah!
gugure! kukure! gugure
繰繰れ！繰繰れ！繰繰れ！
Gugure! Kukure! Gugure!
rereru rerure LOVE★
れれる　れるれー LOVE★
Rereru rerure LOVE★
hi fu mi ah
ひーふーみー 鳴呼
One, two, three, ah!
oh yeah get down boogie
おーいえー　げっだーん　ぶーーぎーー
Oh yeah get down boogie
dance dance dance
だんす　だんす　だんす
Dance, dance, dance
kokon touzai shinkyuu you hou
古今東西　新旧洋邦
All ages past and present, here and across the ocean
ryouri ga dekiru otoko wa moterunda!
料理ができる　男はモテるんだー !
The men should be able to cook!
de? sorede?
で？それで？
And? What of it?
souji mo kanpeki! sentaku mo kanpeki!
掃除も完璧! 洗濯も完璧
Perfect cleaning! Perfect laundry!
airon mo osaihou mo
アイロンも お裁縫も
Ironing and sewing too
ooi shouchu to tako wa sa
おーい焼酎とたこわさー
Hey, get the alcohol and snacks!
jichikai ni mo deterundaze?
自治会にも出てるんだぜ?
How about joining the neighbourhood council too?
go kinjo tsukiai perfect
ご近所付き合いパーフェクト
My relationship with our neighbours is perfect
ha ha
はっは
nanoni nande tei hyouka!
なのに なんで低評価!
And yet why aren't I appreciated?!
hatarake subete wa waga kimi no tame ni
はたらけ全てはわが君のために
Work! It's all for my darling!
subete wa ore no niito seikatsu no tame ni
全ては俺のニート生活のために
It's all for my life as a NEET!
kao wa ii hou darou
顔はいい方だろ
My face looks good, right?
zannen
残念!
Too bad!
kirei na kamishitsu darou
きれいな髪質だろ
My hair is beautiful, right?
shiruga!
白髪!
It's grey!
suiji sentaku wa makasero
炊事洗濯はまかせろ
You can leave the cooking and cleaning to me
okan!
おかん!
Mother!
kamenokou yori toshinokou daro!!
亀の甲より年の功だろ ! !
The older the wiser, right?!
gakugaku iwasezu ni utatte kudasai
ガクガク言わずに歌ってください
Please sing without being outspoken
hai! hai! hai! hai!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
kemo kemo kemo kemoke
ケモケモケモ けもけもけ
ossan nii-san nee-san minasama rasshai!
おっさんにーさんねーさんみなさまらっしゃい！
Old man, brother, sister, everybody come on!
chintonshan! binchoutan!
ちんとんしゃん！びんちょうたん！
tonshan
とんしゃん！
choutan!
ちょうたん！
tarira tarirarira dance! dance! dance!
タリラタリラリラ　ダンス！ダンス！ダンス！
yoisho!
よいしょ！
Heave-ho!
kemo kemo kemo kemo kemoke
ケモケモケモ　けもけもけ
kokuri kokuri burning heart
コクリコクリ　バーニングハート
hanchahan isshohan
半チャーハン 一升半
Half fried rice! Half a bushel!
say say
シェイシェイ
Say, say!
yeah yeah
いえーいえー
Yeah, yeah!
gugure! kukure! gugure!
繰繰れ！繰繰れ！繰繰れ！
Gugure! Kukure! Gugure!
rereru rerure LOVE★
れれる　れるれー LOVE★
Rereru rerure LOVE★
Doki Fansubs | http://doki.co | http://anidex.moe
Haunting 6
"Kohina, the Cyclops, and Shigaraki!"
Your ability to sense the supernatural has
probably grown stronger
because you're always around us.
Listen, Kohina. Most spirits can't
coexist well with humans.
If you don't want to die, don't make
eye contact and don't approach them!
You don't need to be too scared, though.
You've got me.
Kohina!
Don't get eaten right away!
Dolls are not perturbed by digestive juices.
Well, I am, you twerp!
It did put me in its mouth, but I'm not injured.
Don't worry.
You're starting to melt.
Allow me to fix you up.
Harden, harden.
Oh? I got so excited, I overdid it.
There's only one thing to do.
I must soften you up again.
Kohina!
In any case, they're dangerous!
Don't go near them again!
Stomp
I will not go near them.
Are you sure you understand?
Stomp
Yes.
Don't stand like that!
Stomp
I'm worried about you, so take this.
It'll keep spirits away.
Thank you very much.
Use it when you're attacked by evil
spirits or when you're in danger.
When I'm in danger?
Whine.
My darling, please tread on me some more.
That must mean right now.
Stick.
Don't test it on friends! You're wasting it!
Ichimatsu's sixth sense suddenly awakened.
She believed it would change her life completely.
Don't approach them. Don't make eye contact.
However, her life didn't change much.
You're hurt?
Don't make eye contact and
don't approach them!
She treated it from a distance
while avoiding eye contact.
First Aid
It seems to have taken a liking
to her since she treated it.
That's not good, little girl.
The fox is going to be upset.
It just sat on my head.
I haven't even made eye contact with it.
That means I'm safe.
No, you're out!
No means no!
I'll take this spherical cyclops...
Poof
Kokkuri-san divided into two.
...and do this!
And this!
And turn him into a star!
After that, Kokkuri-san ran a home run lap.
Several days later...
The cyclops returned from outer space.
You came back?
I'll hide it before anyone sees it,
and keep it in secret.
Oh, that thing came back?
It was discovered immediately.
Little girl, humans shouldn't try to
domesticate monsters and spirits.
They're stupid creatures that can't
distinguish between good and evil.
It's for your own good.
You should stay away from them.
Old man...
You changed how you look in your tanuki form.
Yeah. I want young girls to make a fuss over me.
I'm cuter this way, right?
Lewd beast.
But this creature is intelligent
enough to learn tricks.
Shake hands.
How's that?!
See? Like this.
It's eating you!
Get off her!
You'll end up with a scar on your hand.
Little girl, you really should
stay away from this thing.
The fox would be sad if
anything happened to you.
I don't want to see a little
girl like you get hurt, either.
Try to understand.
I'll do the responsible thing...
and sell it at a pawn shop.
One that deals in spirits.
Are you sure you don't just want the money?
It's not about the money.
I'm just worried about you, little girl.
You're blinded by money.
I will set it free when it
becomes too dangerous.
Please keep this a secret.
What?
Please.
Guess I've got no choice. I won't say anything.
Only on one condition, though.
I won't say anything, so could
you give me some money?
You are the epitome of scum.
You are the lowest of the low
to ask a child for money.
Oh, stop.
That was not a compliment.
You should get money from Kokkuri-san.
The fox is no help.
He only gives me 500 yen a month.
Don't waste it.
You can't expect an adult
man to survive on 500 yen.
I get five hundred yen a month, too. Also..
Is getting a job not an option for you?
I've gotta stay professionally unemployed.
Very well. I shall give you money.
New Product                Limited Edition Cup Noodles
I resisted buying the sorts of
things that children want,
and spent five years saving up...
all my ten yen coins.
I have roughly 500 of them.
I think I'd have trouble spending
those, on several levels...
I'm going to hide the cyclops,
so could you walk Inugami-san?
It's my turn to walk him today.
Sure, but Inugami wants to
go with you, doesn't he?
You can transform to look like me.
That is your speciality.
Hey, you're right!
I'll give it a shot.
And so, he tried the transformation.
Inugami-san. It's me, Ichimatsu.
I've been waiting for you, my darling.
Let's go for a walk.
What do you think you're doing?
Huh? You could tell?
Is it because my wig is a little
redder than the hair of the real girl?
I'd expect nothing less from her stalker.
Everything about this disguise is wrong.
I am impressed you saw through
his disguise, Inugami-san.
I will praise you for now.
My darling!
However, you cannot get lucky twice in a row.
When the two of us are shuffled at
high speed and then stand together...
Will you be able to guess which
is the real Ichimatsu again?
What are you two trying to do?
Grin
Why don't we make a bet?
If you correctly guess the real Ichimatsu,
you will go for a walk with the old man.
If you're wrong, you'll go for
a walk with the real Ichimatsu.
What?
Now, choose.
In other words, I want to get it wrong.
However, calling this filthy thing
"Kohina-sama" is a test of loyalty!
It would be a betrayal of my love!
However, if I lie, I can go
on a walk with my darling!
I must call this filthy thing "my darling"!
No!
This monster is not my darling!
That's correct.
Let's go for a walk.
Inugami, who remained true to her love,
went for a walk with the fake Kohina.
Little dog lady, if you don't walk,
I'll have to carry you.
A
Wants to Go Home
There's a good girl!
There! I'll reward you by carrying you!
You tricked me!
They will not find you here.
Huh? Kohina.
What are you doing out here?
Go to sleep for a bit.
Ow!
That hurt. What was that for?
He's not sleeping?
Fwump.
That's odd.
In manga and anime, that makes people collapse.
Perhaps I didn't do it enough times.
What? Hey, stop!
I'll go bald!
No!
Kohina... Kohina, you...
You don't get any snacks!
Eat lots and grow big.
And so, Ichimatsu took care
of the cyclops every day.
Good grief.
I thought she'd tire of it pretty quickly,
but she's taking really good care of it.
I wish I could force the fox to babysit these two,
but I promised I'd keep her secret.
She tripped.
Dolls are not perturbed by pain.
She talks about being a
doll even when she's alone.
I am bleeding.
Are you trying to comfort me?
I cannot believe you're a dangerous spirit.
Little girl, we're going home.
I forgot to tell you this,
but you shouldn't give it blood.
I understand.
In other words, it should get its iron
intake not from blood, but from spinach.
That's not what I meant at all, but sure, whatever.
I'm home.
Welcome home. Oh, Shigaraki's with you?
Kohina, you hurt your leg?
Yes. However, it's been licked better,
so it doesn't hurt anymore.
Wait, licked? What did you do?!
I'm innocent.
Time to die.
I thought so.
Once they develop a taste for blood,
they can no longer coexist with humans.
I feel bad for the little girl,
but letting it go would only
allow other children to die.
Damn. It cursed me with its dying breath.
Now, then... How do I go about
explaining this to the little girl?
Man, this won't be easy to tell her.
I'm not one for covering up unpleasant things,
but I could make it so she
can't see them anymore.
I don't want to see a child cry.
Spirits should be nothing more than
dreams humans forget when they wake up.
This isn't a reality she should have to face.
I can't see them.
Kokkuri-san, I can't see the ghosts anymore.
I don't know what happened, but that's great.
My darling, you're looking beautiful again today.
There's a cut on your face.
Yeah.
He probably got scratched by
some girl he was hitting on.
Yeah, something like that.
You vulgar barbarian.
I can't see the cyclops.
I can never see the cyclops again.
Little girl, I understand that you're sad
you can't see your friend anymore,
but he was never meant to coexist with humans.
Don't be so down about it.
I am sad.
I was thinking of using him as
a topping for my cup noodles.
How disappointing.
I fed him cup noodles every day.
He should have soaked up their flavours by now.
I think making food out of him
is a bit too adventurous.
The old man acted behind the
scenes to protect a girl's dreams,
and earned himself a scar over his eye.
When he learned it was all for cup
noodles, he became very nervous.
oboete iru kana
覚えているかな
I wonder if you remember
ichiban kanashii toki
一番悲しい時
Your saddest moment
yokei na kotoba wo
余計な言葉を
Needless words
minna sutete kureta
みんな捨ててくれた
Have been cast aside
karappo no ude ni
空っぽの腕に
Wrapped under my arms
sotto mogurikonde
そっと潜り込んで
I've been crouching down
sameta jounetsu
冷めた情熱
The cooled down passion
atatame nagara
温めながら
Starts to warm up again
taisetsu na mono ga
大切なものが
What's precious to me
koko ni hitotsu dake
ここにひとつだけ
There is only one thing
arifureta hibi ni
ありふれた日々に
In these mundane days
shizuka ni nagareru merodi
静かに流れるメロディ
A melody is quietly passing through
issho ni utawanakute mo ii kara
一緒に歌わなくてもいいから
We don't need to sing together
kono mama tenpo ni makasete hoshii
このままテンポに任せて欲しい
I want to leave it to our current tempo
mawaru mawatte
回る　回って
It goes around and around
hikari no naka de
光の中で
Inside the light
mawaru mawatte
回る　回って
It goes around and around
kurikaeshite
繰り返して
Over and over again
Sometimes even Inugami-san wants
some quiet time to himself.
When he does, Inugami-san drinks coffee.
When the smell of the coffee attracts
a certain hairball, it ruins the mood.
Inugami, are you making coffee again?
I'm pretty fond of the smell of this coffee.
Well, well, I'm so glad you like it.
You're welcome to enjoy the
smell as much as you like.
You hate me so much,
you start grilling mackerel?
Yes, I dislike you. I absolutely hate you.
Why?
I feed you, and I take you for most of your walks!
I'm practically your owner!
Why do you hate me so much?
Why? Why do you want to know?
I want to know if you hate me because
I did something wrong to you!
If I really did something wrong, I'd make it right!
Is that so? Very well.
Please don't complain once I've told you.
Fine! Bring it on, damn it!
Allow me to read all 100,005,000
reasons why I hate you.
What I Hate About the Fox
All the Reasons Why I Hate the Fox
There are that many?! Keep it short!
I hate the way you give me orders.
I hate your long hair.
Hate your long hair!
I hate how fluffy you are.
Fluffy
Seriously?
I hate that you're a man who can do housework.
Man who does housework
What?
I hate how nice you are to everyone.
Nice to everyone
Come on!
I just fundamentally hate you!
See? You asked me to tell you,
and now you're sulking.
I hate the way you invite pain upon yourself.
Finally...
There is a single, greatest reason I hate you.
You want to know what it is?
What is it?!
It's this...
I fundamentally hate you because
you're not Kohina-sama.
That means you hate nearly
everyone in the world!
That's right. I hate everything
other than Kohina-sama.
You're sick in the head!
In addition to hating people, I hate
stars, the sky, flowers... everything.
What?
Do you even hate flowers that bloom in asphalt?
I hate them. So what?
What?!
If you hate everything but Kohina,
does that mean you hate yourself?
Of course I do.
What?
There's a therapist by the station, you know.
Don't tell me I need to see a doctor.
Curses are my nature.
I am the spirit of a dog tortured
to death who curses the world.
It's natural for me to hate everything.
I guess so.
But there is something I like other than my darling.
What's that?
The suffering of others.
You're scum!
I believe there are plenty of other people
who hate the world and themselves.
You think so?
In my case, as long as my darling loves me,
I think I could learn to like other things just a little.
However, when I imagine my darling hating me...
You're an eyesore, you filthy mongrel.
It excites me!
Why are you suddenly gushing blood?!
Oh, dear. My coffee got cold while I was
answering your ridiculous questions.
I don't feel like drinking cold coffee.
Come to think of it, I didn't
serve a drink to my guest.
Have some coffee.
Don't give me something you don't want!
Now, now. I'll serve a light snack, too.
Have this mackerel I just finished grilling.
Stink
You were still grilling that?
Now, I suppose I shall start over
and make some fresh coffee.
Hey, wait! Don't make some just for yourself!
Next Time
Haunting 7             Inugami's Love at First Sight!
This Week's Fluff: Niko-chan
Oh? It's a cat again.
It's a meow-meow.
I wonder if there really are more cat people.
Dogs are cute, too.
Bark, bark.