Once upon a time, there was a place where an old man and woman lived.
The old man took care of the land,
and the old lady washed clothes at the river.
There! There!
Right then, a big peach came floating.
What's that?!
...and so I carried it here.
And? Are you going to eat this weird peach, you hag?
I'm not a hag! Call me "old woman"!
The colour is good, and it looks delicious.
How nice, I can eat it alone, too!
There!
I'm Momotaro.
There was a baby inside the peach!
H-How cute! No, beautiful!
My darling? My darling!
This is how Momotaro, born from a peach, came to the old couple.
Momotaro, having grown, left to defeat
a demon harassing the people of the world.
My darling!
Please don't go defeat a demon!
Please always stay with us!
Don't hold Momotaro back when she's leaving!
Here, Momotaro, take these sweet dumplings with you.
Feed them to animals, make them your companions, and defeat the demon together.
Thank you, old woman.
But I prefer cup noodles-
Just take the sweet dumplings.
Okay.
Old man, old woman, thank you for everything.
Don't go after all, Kohina!
My darling!
Recommended with dog, monkey and pheasant,
it says on the dumplings' user manual.
Right then, Momotaro came upon a fateful meeting.
*Stare*
Little girl, do you have anything to eat?
I think I'm about to starve to death.
Please show mercy to me.
I only have these sweet dumplings my old woman made.
Thank you!
Little girl, I owe my life to you!
If you eat the dumplings, you have to help defeat the demon.
Mister Tanuki, please become my companion.
What, seriously?
Well, whatever!
All right, leave it to me!
After the tanuki ate all the dumplings,
he and Ichimatsu headed for the Demon Island.
And then...
Thanks to his tricks, the demons lost all the gold,
silver and treasure they had stolen from the people.
Ichimatsu beat the demons just by eating their evening meal cup noodles.
All's well that ends well.
"Momotaro's Companion?"