This story took place shortly after
Kokkuri-san started to haunt Kohina.
She hasn't asked me to leave lately.
I think she's become attached to me.
By the way, Kokkuri-san,
are you going to stick around?
Hm, I wonder.
Wouldn't you be lonely without me?
Not really.
After that, Kokkuri-san was in a world of his own for a week.
Not really... So I was the only one who thought we were friends...
Without hesitation...
What's this one-sidedness?
Bothersome... Not really... I don't care... Whatever...
Kokkuri-san is an adult who's easily hurt.
My cooking is worse than those 3 minute meals?
Is that what you're trying to say?
Well?
Not really... Not really... Not really...
I'm just an unneeded fox...
I don't matter at all...
Not really... Not really... Not really...
My words seem to have hurt Kokkuri-san.
Even as a doll, I know what to say in cases like this.
Not really... Whatever... Not Really...
Kokkuri-san.
Kohina?
You're annoying.
Annoying...
You even said it twice!
I repeated it because it's important.
You're the first person ever to annoy a doll to this extent.
Onii-san is about to stop breathing...
Having feelings means defeat for a doll.
If you weren't like a ten-year-old made of glass, this wouldn't have happened.
A ten-year-old...?!
As an apology...
This will be a token of our friendship.
Huh? Friendship?
Just kidding.
A
Kokkuri-san receives Bell of Friendship!
But this equipment is cursed.
Huh? What's this?!
I can't get it off!
Cup noodles!
Cup noodles! Cup noodles!
Wait, Kohina!
Kohina-san?!
And so, Kokkuri-san got a cursed bell.
Frankly, he wished none of this had happened, and just wanted to go home.
"Kokkuri-san and the Bell of Friendship!"