It happened one afternoon...
I fell in love at first sight.
How beautiful.
I must make it mine.
hanchahan isshohan
半チャーハン 一升半
Half fried rice! Half a bushel!
say say
シェイシェイ
Say, say!
yeah yeah
いえーいえー
Yeah, yeah!
gugure! kukure! gugure
繰繰れ！繰繰れ！繰繰れ！
Gugure! Kukure! Gugure!
rereru rerure LOVE★
れれる　れるれー LOVE★
Rereru rerure LOVE★
hi fu mi ah
ひーふーみー 鳴呼
One, two, three, ah!
oh yeah get down boogie
おーいえー　げっだーん　ぶーーぎーー
Oh yeah get down boogie
dance dance dance
だんす　だんす　だんす
Dance, dance, dance
kokon touzai shinkyuu you hou
古今東西　新旧洋邦
All ages past and present, here and across the ocean
ryouri ga dekiru otoko wa moterunda!
料理ができる　男はモテるんだー !
The men should be able to cook!
de? sorede?
で？それで？
And? What of it?
souji mo kanpeki! sentaku mo kanpeki!
掃除も完璧! 洗濯も完璧
Perfect cleaning! Perfect laundry!
airon mo osaihou mo
アイロンも お裁縫も
Ironing and sewing too
ooi shouchu to tako wa sa
おーい焼酎とたこわさー
Hey, get the alcohol and snacks!
jichikai ni mo deterundaze?
自治会にも出てるんだぜ?
How about joining the neighbourhood council too?
go kinjo tsukiai perfect
ご近所付き合いパーフェクト
My relationship with our neighbours is perfect
ha ha
はっは
nanoni nande tei hyouka!
なのに なんで低評価!
And yet why aren't I appreciated?!
hatarake subete wa waga kimi no tame ni
はたらけ全てはわが君のために
Work! It's all for my darling!
subete wa ore no niito seikatsu no tame ni
全ては俺のニート生活のために
It's all for my life as a NEET!
kao wa ii hou darou
顔はいい方だろ
My face looks good, right?
zannen
残念!
Too bad!
kirei na kamishitsu darou
きれいな髪質だろ
My hair is beautiful, right?
shiruga!
白髪!
It's grey!
suiji sentaku wa makasero
炊事洗濯はまかせろ
You can leave the cooking and cleaning to me
okan!
おかん!
Mother!
kamenokou yori toshinokou daro!!
亀の甲より年の功だろ ! !
The older the wiser, right?!
gakugaku iwasezu ni utatte kudasai
ガクガク言わずに歌ってください
Please sing without being outspoken
hai! hai! hai! hai!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
kemo kemo kemo kemoke
ケモケモケモ けもけもけ
ossan nii-san nee-san minasama rasshai!
おっさんにーさんねーさんみなさまらっしゃい！
Old man, brother, sister, everybody come on!
chintonshan! binchoutan!
ちんとんしゃん！びんちょうたん！
tonshan
とんしゃん！
choutan!
ちょうたん！
tarira tarirarira dance! dance! dance!
タリラタリラリラ　ダンス！ダンス！ダンス！
yoisho!
よいしょ！
Heave-ho!
kemo kemo kemo kemo kemoke
ケモケモケモ　けもけもけ
kokuri kokuri burning heart
コクリコクリ　バーニングハート
hanchahan isshohan
半チャーハン 一升半
Half fried rice! Half a bushel!
say say
シェイシェイ
Say, say!
yeah yeah
いえーいえー
Yeah, yeah!
gugure! kukure! gugure!
繰繰れ！繰繰れ！繰繰れ！
Gugure! Kukure! Gugure!
rereru rerure LOVE★
れれる　れるれー LOVE★
Rereru rerure LOVE★
Doki Fansubs | http://doki.co | http://anidex.moe
Haunting 7
"Cat God Tama's Love at First Sight!"
Lately...
Every time I go outside,
I feel the same girl watching me.
Doesn't it look like that girl's interested in you?
You're imagining things.
Besides, I don't intend to date anyone.
What a waste. She's a real cutie.
Yeah, you think everyone is cute.
It's probably only a matter of time
until she confesses her feelings.
Um, I'd like to speak with you.
I'm stuck...
It was love at first sight.
I just want it so, so much.
I can't stand making girls cry.
If it's all right with you, um...
Could you give me that doll?
Huh?
Th-This isn't a confession?
If there's a confession to be made,
it's that I have a fetish for macabre dolls.
What? Wait...
Did you think I wanted you?
Ugh.
What an embarrassing misunderstanding!
I'll take advantage of your
humiliation to steal your doll!
H-Hey, wait! That's not a-
It's so cute! It's so cute!
It's so soft and squishy!
Doll, are you made from
urethane resin or silicon resin?
You're silicon, aren't you?
I can tell. Just look at these details.
How are you made inside?
What do your insides look like?
Sniff, sniff... Pant, pant, pant...
Who made you? Who made you?
Police!
Who the hell are you?!
I'm turning you over to the police!
Meow...
Me?
I am Tama, the cat god.
I'm the poster girl of the Japanese café,
Nennekotei, down on 3rd Street.
Right.
They call me "Tama of 3rd Street" for short.
Don't shorten it to that.
Now that I've introduced myself,
give me the doll!
No chance!
Just name your price.
She's not for sale.
Look closely! She's a human, not a doll!
I am a doll.
Human
Doll
Which is it?
You're complicating matters!
I am a doll... a doll...
...a doll... a doll... a doll... a doll...
The doll says she's a doll, so she must be a doll.
...a doll.
Dolls don't call themselves dolls.
You think this fleshy thing that's
suppler than ASIMO is inorganic?
Think about it.
There's no way a girl this cute is human!
How stupid of me to expect someone
else to have common sense, damn it!
You think a grown man who
carries around and talks to
a girl doll has common sense?
Sh-She's not a doll, though.
I may not be a doll,
but you are a middle-aged, fox-eared cosplayer
who drags a little girl around with him.
As a girl, I am a much more
suitable owner for the doll!
No, I am the most suitable!
You'll complicate this even
more! Stay out of it!
You're not in love with the fox, then?
I only have eyes for the doll.
I can't believe he misunderstood
just because our eyes met!
How embarrassing.
Stop this.
Kokkuri-san is a handsome and popular man.
He couldn't help the misunderstanding.
Kohina! You're defending me?
But he is only handsome
according to his backstory,
so he only gets attention from background girls.
That was the killing blow!
Now, more importantly, about your doll.
How about exchanging it for my doll?
I told you, Kohina isn't a doll!
Do dolls move? Do they speak?
No!
But my dolls move!
Let's play. Let's play. Let's play.
Their hair grows! Gross!
Mama. Mama. Mama.
They're so cute. How rude, meow.
Is that how she sees Kohina, too?
Scary, gross, and ugly.
They had the three worst
possible qualities for a doll.
Japanese Café Nennekotei
I managed to chase her off.
You have one weird girl after you, Kohina.
Kohina? Huh?
Are you dead?
Just kidding.
Kohina?
Move away from her.
My darling is currently in training.
Lately, she's been neglecting her doll backstory,
so she's training to become more doll-like.
I see. That's why she's acting like a doll.
The Bird That
Never Moves
"The Shoebill"
The Bird That
Never Moves
"The Shoebill"
No. Apparently, she's mimicking a shoebill.
That has nothing to do with dolls!
Little girl, it's time for your snack.
Today's snack is cup noodles.
Are you imitating something again?
Fine, then.
I'll carry you like a doll.
Shigaraki-dono! I won't let you get ahead of me!
What's wrong, little girl? You won't
grow up big if you don't eat.
Open wide, my darling.
Wait a minute! Something's not right!
Do you really think this is Kohina?
Now that you mention it, it's weird that
she doesn't respond to the cup noodles.
She smells different.
Why can't you tell from her appearance?
That cat girl must have switched
her out with this thing!
Let's go save her! Come on, guys!
Yeah!
Don't come with us!
Japanese Café Nennekotei
Welcome to Nennekotei!
Starting today, you're mine, meow.
Doll, do you like anmitsu?
I think the food tastes good,
but this café is always deserted.
Maybe it's just in a bad location, meow.
It's definitely because of the interior décor.
Anyway, I'll give you a name.
I've already thought of one.
My name is Kohina.
Okiku-chan? What a wonderful name!
You misheard it for the name
you wanted to give me?
Is there something wrong with Okiku-chan?
You are being rude.
I am Ichimatsu.
I feel uncomfortable. I'm leaving.
I'll give you this if you'll be my Okiku-chan.
I cannot be bribed with a
single serving of cup noodles.
Don't mock me.
It's an exclusive Nennekotei original.
And so, Ichimatsu began living with Tama.
I can't get in.
The barrier won't let us get close.
I will try it right away.
Go ahead.
"Cream and Anmitsu Flavor"
Not a moment's hesitation!
She's a daring one!
Damn it.
The barrier isn't going away.
We have to find a way to remove it!
Not you!
We should ask Google-sensei.
You're wrong if you think
Sensei knows everything!
Japanese Café Nennekotei
Fox-dono, the instructions
for dispelling the barrier
Japanese Café Nennekotei
are written on the café's homepage.
Seriously?!
Japanese Café Nennekotei
In order to enter the barrier...
"You need the Demon King's sword.
To acquire the sword,
you must defeat the Demon King.
To defeat the Demon King,
you need the legendary sword.
To acquire the sword, you must gather
its pieces scattered around the world,
and free the captured legendary smith-"
What is this, an RPG?
I'll write a bad review for the café on T***log!
I'll tear down her stronghold!
It already only has one star.
Damn it!
Kokkuri-san and crew began attacking
in whatever ways they could.
I don't get it!
Meanwhile, Ichimatsu had
become a dress-up doll.
Dolls really do look best in kimonos.
Your animal form is a cat.
That's right.
Would you like to play?
I don't play.
That won't work.
No, this is... This isn't what it looks like!
Cats aren't so bad, either.
Or so Ichimatsu thought...
But Tama turned out to be more
demanding than Kokkuri-san.
No, no, no!
When you bow slightly,
you only bend 15 degrees!
All my dolls must recite the Hundred
Poems by a Hundred Poets from memory!
As you please.
My dolls do not groan!
They must say "sharanra" instead!
Don't you tempt my doll, demon! I come first!
Death to cup noodles!
Sharanra...
The doll was exhausted by Tama's
frightfully strict supervision.
This is unforgivable.
Catnip!
One hit!
"Water Bottle Obliteration Formation"
Two hit!
I can't get out! What is this?
Cat, your mother is here to see you.
My mum?
But she's a shamisen now.
No!
No, no, no!
Three hit! KO!
Just kidding.
Kohina defeated the cat and headed home.
Fighting is always fruitless.
My darling!
Gah!
Yay!
On the property Ichimatsu's home is built on,
there is a storehouse that was
constructed before the Meiji era.
I haven't been keeping this
place clean. It's full of junk.
Cleaning this place will be backbreaking work.
Do Not Open This Box
Don't open it. Seriously, don't open it.
Seeing that written on it just
makes me want to open it.
It seems that carelessly touching any
object in this storehouse curses you.
I-I'm a woman?
Oh, no! I can't transform back!
What's going on?
Was it the box?
What's this piece of paper?
Maybe it'll help me return to...
I told you not to open it (lol)
Terrible! Whoever wrote this is terrible!
Normally, you'd leave a clue
as to how to return to normal!
This isn't good.
I can't let them see me like this.
Not...
Not in this lovely form.
Kokkuri-san is a bit of a narcissist.
Stare.
She saw me!
You're a woman.
Yeah. It happened when
I opened a strange box.
Most of the objects in the Ichimatsu
family's storehouse are cursed.
If you're not careful, you'll die.
Are you sure your house isn't
connected to the spirit world?
There's probably a piece of paper explaining how to turn back to normal inside the box.
There was only an aggravating
piece of paper in there!
If you hold aggravating paper up
to the light, words will appear.
What?!
But I turned that paper into ash!
Why would you do something so confusing?
The dying wish of the first head
of the Ichimatsu family was to put
confusing pieces of paper inside cursed boxes.
Did he do it to prevent others from getting
their hands on the family's magic?
No.
It was simply so he could watch people
get frustrated again and again.
You have a really nasty family!
By the way, Kohina, what do
you think of me as a woman?
Am I cute? Am I beautiful?
What do I think?
You're neither spirit-like nor fox-like.
Your only identifying
characteristic is how you like
doing housework even though you're a man.
It's not even that unusual
in the 3D world these days.
When you become just another
woman who likes housework,
that distinction fades, and your already
weak personality grows even weaker.
You need to find another quality to promote.
I wasn't asking for an editor's opinion.
Kokkuri-san had the vague feeling
that his situation was critical.
Kohina, are there any other clues besides
that paper on how to return to normal?
I don't know.
Why don't you ask the others
if they can break the curse?
That's terrifying!
We're talking about a demon
who lives to harass me,
and an old pervert who will hit on
anything with two X chromosomes!
I'll strengthen the curse.
I'll examine your body thoroughly.
They would traumatize me with shame!
Kohina, let's run away together!
Let's go somewhere the two
of them will never find us!
Tomorrow, I have a quiz that won't affect
my grade, so you're free to go by yourself.
You turned me down for the
lamest reason possible!
What are you two going on about?
My darling!
The demons found out in no time.
Oh?
He locked on to his target.
Fox...
What?
H-He's going to sexually harass me!
I'll work.
I'll quit drinking, smoking, and gambling, too!
What? Wai-
Marry me.
No!
I'm a man! I'd never accept
your proposal, you idiot!
What?
Find someone else!
But we're close in age,
and we know each other well.
You're beautiful, great at housework,
and love taking care of people!
You think I'll find another virgin who fulfils
Virgin
all those conditions in this day and age?!
Don't call me a virgin, you idiot!
The only problem is, you're middle-aged...
Who are you calling middle-aged?
That was a nice kick.
So when should we make it rain?
A "fox's wedding" is not happening!
Listen to me!
Do you want me to make it rain blood?
No, I'll listen.
Really?
Yeah, it's important. I want you
to make your own choice.
Do you prefer a white
kimono or a wedding dress?
You've already decided to add
me to your family register?
His choices were very limited.
Where do you want to go for our honeymoon?
Go by yourself!
By the way, "chasing women" was not among
the things you said you'd stop doing.
Are you going to cheat on her?
What?
Of course I won't cheat!
I don't think I will.
I probably won't.
What is this, a "Kanpaku Sengen" reference?
Don't make jokes teenagers won't understand.
I want to lift the curse somehow.
Can't you do something, Shigaraki?
There is one way.
Really?
I can't guarantee it'll work, but it's
an old technique without much risk.
It's worth trying.
The Actually Dirty Grimms' Fairy Tales
Fox, have you heard of the frog prince?
Anything but that.
It's all right. Just close your eyes.
It's not all right!
You shouldn't be obstinate
during an emergency.
Don't say things that sound so legit!
If you keep pressing your luck, I'll hit you.
You already hit him.
Ouch...
It was just a little joke.
I'm a gentleman.
No, you were serious!
Will Kokkuri-san become the old man's bride?
Why did Kokkuri-san really resist
becoming a woman so much?
Find out in the next episode.
Kohina, however, was more concerned with the piece of leek that got stuck in her teeth at lunch.
Take that.
oboete iru kana
覚えているかな
I wonder if you remember
ichiban kanashii toki
一番悲しい時
Your saddest moment
yokei na kotoba wo
余計な言葉を
Needless words
minna sutete kureta
みんな捨ててくれた
Have been cast aside
karappo no ude ni
空っぽの腕に
Wrapped under my arms
sotto mogurikonde
そっと潜り込んで
I've been crouching down
sameta jounetsu
冷めた情熱
The cooled down passion
atatame nagara
温めながら
Starts to warm up again
taisetsu na mono ga
大切なものが
What's precious to me
koko ni hitotsu dake
ここにひとつだけ
There is only one thing
arifureta hibi ni
ありふれた日々に
In these mundane days
shizuka ni nagareru merodi
静かに流れるメロディ
A melody is quietly passing through
issho ni utawanakute mo ii kara
一緒に歌わなくてもいいから
We don't need to sing together
kono mama tenpo ni makasete hoshii
このままテンポに任せて欲しい
I want to leave it to our current tempo
mawaru mawatte
回る　回って
It goes around and around
hikari no naka de
光の中で
Inside the light
mawaru mawatte
回る　回って
It goes around and around
kurikaeshite
繰り返して
Over and over again
Next Time
Haunting 8          Kokkuri-san's Steamy Secret Hot Spring Tour!
This Week's Fluff: Chako-chan
Wow! That's a super close-up of a dog!
What an energetic doggie!
W-What's wrong? Calm down.