Kokkuri-san is proud of his fluffy tail,
and thinks Kohina and the kids in the
neighbourhood are in love with it.
One day, his precious tail...
came off!
Riichi.
What is it?
Th-This...
This is no time to be laughing!
This is my fluffiest part!
For your tail to come off...
How careless of you.
There was nothing I could have done, it suddenly came off!
Hey, what's with your tail?!
Is there something wrong with my tail?
"Something wrong?", my ass!
Isn't it different than usual?!
"Who cares", is what Ichimatsu thought.
Hm?
"Hm", my ass!
That tail... Could it be a fake?
Something like a wig?
You two can't fool me that easily!
Chainsaw!
Damn, it was real?!
That hurt!
You... That...
Uh, are you okay?
It's just a tail, it'll grow back in no time.
Another different tail?
K-Kohina...
Y-You, what are you doing?!
Give it back! That pretty tail belongs to me!
Give it back!
I'm all fluffy!
My... My fluffiness...
Kokkuri-san, you are no longer fluffy.
Please don't call yourself fluffy anymore.
After sewing it on,
Kokkuri-san had his tail back.
"Your tail came off?"