It's December 24th.
Everyone is in high spirits.
Dolls do not get excited by Christmas.
I am going to purchase a party bucket
of chicken for Kokkuri-san, then go home.
I shall execute my mission
in a stoic... fashion...
Radio-Controlled Cup Noodles
Now on Sale!!
It Drives!
Radio-Controlled Cup Noodles
Imagine that...
It Drives!
Radio-Controlled Cup Noodles
I can buy it with my chicken money.
Buy it. If you say dropped your purse,
he won't know you're lying.
You mustn't lie.
Don't lie to yourself.
You must obey your desires.
Yes, my angel.
Hey.
Doki Fansubs | http://doki.co | http://anidex.moe
You're a c-cutie. Do... you want that?
Do you want me to buy it for you?
In exchange, we can... together...
Just as Ichimatsu was about to commit a sin,
God sent a suspicious man to her.
Do what together?!
You creep!
Were you going to play doctor?
Were you going to play doctor in the dark?!
Pervert!
No!
With palpations, too?
I'll palpate you!
Are you okay, Kohina?
It's terrible how many
perverts are around, huh?
Kokkuri-san, did you follow me?
Yeah, I was worried about you.
I was watching over you from the shadows.
I saw you filch the chicken money, too.
My attempt failed.
How dare you suddenly kick
and punch me like that?
I'll sue.
He's alive!
Stare.
What? You...
Why do you have those ears?
And those clothes...
A tail!??
White?
Are you...
Ears?
White?
A ghost?!
It was the first time Kokkuri-san had
actually been treated like a ghost.
I finally spooked someone.
A g-ghost?!
That's right. I'm a super scary ghost...
And I will get you.
I will get you.
The Gaze of Cocytus
Once he'd calmed down,
he was embarrassed.
The Gaze of Cocytus
Shiver
Tremble
Th-This is terrifying...
Shiver
Tremble
Hey, now. Calm down.
Shiver
Tremble
I can't believe you're a ghost!
Shiver
Tremble
How am I supposed to sue you?!
That's what scares you?!
I have a phobia of things I cannot sue.
What kind of condition is that?
Now that's terrifying...
Um, I'm a lawyer.
It's a work-related condition?!
I'm sorry for giving you the
wrong impression and scaring you.
I wanted you to help me choose a
Christmas present for my daughter.
You look like you're around her age.
So that was why.
I came across as suspicious
because I was nervous.
Embarrassingly enough, um...
I'm not very good with children.
Because they can't be tried
under criminal law, you see.
Though, you can sue their parents.
Who would dislike children for that reason?!
As you can see, I'm a workaholic.
I haven't fulfilled any fatherly
duties for my daughter.
I took a long, hard look at myself
and regretted how negligent I've been.
Just once, I'd like to create
some memories with my child.
I figured I could at least get
her a Christmas present...
I see.
In that case, we'll help.
After all, we're both guardians.
Ah, thank you very much.
So, do you know what you want to give her?
Stare...
Actually, I have no idea what girls are into.
I thought a book about the six major
legal codes would make a good gift.
Heavy
The thickness, and this curved edge...
Forget about your job!
Yes, sir.
Haunting 12
Thank you for coming with me.
It's fine.
I'm glad I met you.
Given my disposition,
the other girls I tried talking to
wouldn't respond or even look at me.
I'm glad I stuck with it and asked around
two or three hundred young girls for help.
Pant
I'm surprised no one
reported you to the police.
Listen...
Try not to think about work.
I'm sorry.
You should ask a girl about what girls like.
Kohina, what do you think he should get?
As a girl...
I would recommend
radio-controlled cup noodles!
Gimme
Gimme!
We're not getting anything
that only you would like.
Gimme
I was stupid to expect anything from you.
All I know is what kind
of cup noodles girls like.
Girls like accessories, don't they?
Pendants and rings...
Brooches and badges...
Badges?
I have my lawyer's badge right here!
I told you to forget about your job!
You should ask your
daughter what she wants.
What? Don't you think it's better
to surprise someone with a gift?
If you choose a gift together,
you can communicate with one another.
But I'm not sure I can have a proper
conversation with my daughter.
I may be able to speak to her,
but I left her alone for so long.
I don't think she likes me.
Besides, if she charges me with neglect...
Neglect
Don't view your own child that way!
Also, stop being afraid of lawsuits!
Neglect
You'll never get anywhere like that!
Instead of just getting her a present,
throw her a Christmas party!
I'll set up a situation for you to
have a real conversation with her!
Don't sweat the small stuff!
You'd do that for me?
Yeah, I'll do it!
Th-Thank you!
I can't thank you enough!
Kokkuri-san, if you're ever charged
with anything, come speak to me!
I won't be!
Anyway, Kohina's tired and starting to get bored.
Let's finish our shopping.
Gape
My daughter, Noelle, is probably home alone again
since my wife will be home late tonight.
It's been so long since I've seen her.
I'm not sure she'll even speak to me.
They're about to face each other.
Noelle?
I'm home.
I don't give a flyin' flip about Christmas!
Non-Alcoholic
Stupid couples!
Is it so wrong to spend it alone?
They're all a buncha fools,
gettin' so excited over it!
I ain't like those puppets
of the commercial media!
It's a Christian holiday, anyhow!
It ain't got nothin' to do with me!
Wow.
She seemed rather depraved.
Was that dialect Hiroshima, or just manly?
Why are you shaking? Get in there.
Oh, I know. I'll give you a good luck charm.
As long as you're wearing this ribbon,
you'll be able to talk with your daughter.
Just relax.
Que sera, sera.
I feel like I can do it!
Hooray! Hooray! Hooray!
Kokkuri-san, don't you think you're
being too nice to the old man?
I-It's not like that!
How suspicious.
Noelle? Do you want to celebrate
Christmas with your dad this year?
Whaddya think you're doing?!
It's too late for you to act like a father!
Instead of ignoring me, she responded!
I'm so glad!
His standards are very low.
Anyway, I regret my behaviour...
Why don't we all throw a
Christmas party together?
This sudden change of heart
doesn't make me happy at all.
A Christmas party?
I'm totally... not really... interested in that.
But I don't have plans,
s-so it's not like I can't come to your party...
I'm sure you have a party bucket, right?
Here.
A party bucket...
If we're going to have a party,
hurry up and get stuff ready!
I don't have a lot of time!
You should've told me you
were bringing guests with you!
It seems she's actually quite the tsundere.
I mean, I hate Christmas, you know!
What a pain in the ass.
She looks so happy.
This is my first time spending
Christmas with someone.
Kohina...
I've always spent Christmas alone.
Sacrifice?
I usually hold a black mass to
strengthen my doll powers.
Sacrifice?
Elohim essaim, elohim essaim...
You're a pro at playing by yourself.
Look at the time.
Time flies, doesn't it?
It's sad how quickly good
times come to an end.
Old man.
It's time for us to go.
You're leaving?
No.
That good luck charm should
be wearing off soon.
I see. Yes, of course.
That's too bad.
Wait outside. I'd like just a little
more time with her before I go.
Thank you for waiting.
I tricked her.
I wanted her to spend today
in the spirit of Christmas.
I just told her I'd be going
somewhere far away for a bit.
I see.
Are you ready to go now?
Yes. Thanks to you, I'm ready to cross over.
Cross over?
I didn't say anything because
I didn't want to scare you,
but I'm already dead.
I was involved in an incident a while ago.
The public probably still thinks I'm missing.
They say the only cure for stupidity is death,
but the same can be said for workaholism.
No, you're still a workaholic.
Now that I'm dead, I've realized
something, looking back.
I hated my workaholic father.
When I looked at him, I always told
myself I would never become him.
But, overwhelmed by my everyday life,
I eventually became the same kind of adult.
Even though I'd experienced that loneliness
and resentment, I did the exact same thing.
By the time I came to regret that,
I couldn't get my family to notice me.
All I could do for my family was stand
by their beds and paralyse them.
What an awful form of communication.
Thanks to you,
I was able to make a good memory in the end.
Thank you.
After saying these words, the man
crossed over into the next life.
He didn't have a shadow
because he was a ghost.
You noticed his shadow was missing?
Yes.
I thought he simply lacked presence.
That's not the same thing.
If they find his body and
realize he died before today,
won't his daughter think
today's events were impossible,
and that it was all a dream?
No need to worry about that.
We left proof.
You mean the present?
No, proof a ghost was there.
A paranormal photo.
Come to think of it, I feel like
we've forgotten something.
I'm going on a date with a lady
The chicken is taking a long time, my darling.
Inugami-san waited alone for Ichimatsu
and Kokkuri-san to return.
Growl
New Year's Eve
Nothing beats a kotatsu in winter.
Once you get in, you can't get out again.
I agree.
Absolutely.
Come on, guys!
Don't lounge around! We have to clean today!
Huh?
Everyone, man your stations and
carry out your duties, post haste!
It's time to start cleaning!
Shazam
Yeah.
Let's do this!
Stare.
Take this, dust! Take this!
Be cleaned!
I'll get out all the filth that's built up in here.
Cozy
Aw, crap.
Hey!
Get cleaning!
Cozy
Stop relaxing!
In the end, Ichimatsu was made to clean when
her New Year's money was taken hostage.
Since Kokkuri-san always keeps the place so tidy,
it isn't necessary to clean too often.
My darling.
Can I do anything to help?
A simple job even Inugami-san can do...
Please take out the garbage.
You want me to take out
all the garbage I see?
Yes.
Take out... the garbage.
Who told you to raze the whole area?
Everything but you is garbage, my darling.
Cute
You're the garbage, you mongrel!
Twinkle!
Ouch...
Inugami-san got into serious
trouble for over-cleaning.
Time for New Year's soba.
Here it comes.
Fluff
I panicked a little when everything got razed,
but I'm glad we were able to repair it.
I'll let you smell it.
I can't reach, Fox-dono!
It would have been terrible if we hadn't had the Ichimatsu family's seven balls of wish-granting.
Why is your family's storehouse
full of legendary items?
Well, whatever.
The food's hot. Be careful.
Okay.
Let's eat!
Yum! This is good!
Little girl, want some seven-flavour chili pepper?
No.
I shall use cup noodles as a topping.
Drop the cup noodles.
That's the New Year's bell.
The year is over.
So it is.
Yes.
Huh? Inugami, have you gotten smaller?
Huh?
Did your worldly desires shrink,
making you that much smaller?
He shrank again.
No! My darling, help-
Inugami disappeared!
Inugami!
New Year's Day
And so, the new year arrived.
It's a shrine.
A
Forced by
Kokkuri-san
to wear her
best clothes
Is there any point in visiting a
shrine when you're a former god?
Yeah. It's all about enjoying
things like this in spirit.
Well, you may be a former god,
but you were more like a divine
messenger or part-time god.
He's never been invited to Izumo in
the tenth month of the Japanese calendar.
Oh, my.
Don't bring that up!
Kokkuri-san, what are you going to wish for?
I don't know.
Humans are fragile.
They die in an instant.
It would be painful to say goodbye again.
Our lives are too slow to live with
humans, and too long to live alone.
If I could have a wish...
I wish the time I have now would last forever.
hanchahan isshohan
半チャーハン 一升半
Half fried rice! Half a bushel!
say say
シェイシェイ
Say, say!
yeah yeah
いえーいえー
Yeah, yeah!
gugure! kukure! gugure
繰繰れ！繰繰れ！繰繰れ！
Gugure! Kukure! Gugure!
rereru rerure LOVE★
れれる　れるれー LOVE★
Rereru rerure LOVE★
hi fu mi ah
ひーふーみー 鳴呼
One, two, three, ah!
oh yeah disco baby
おーいえー　でいすこ　べいべー
dance dance dance
だんす　だんす　だんす
Dance, dance, dance
ittai zentai nandemotte
いったいぜんたい　なんでもって
Why on earth
matomo na yatsu ga hitori mo inainda!
まともなやつが一人もいないんだー！
Is there not one decent guy around here!
suki na hito wa nijuuyon jikan issho ni inakya deshou
好きな人とは２４時間一緒にいなきゃでしょう
You have to like the person to be with them for 24 hours
yappari otoko wa hataraitara make ga na to omotteru
やっぱり男は働いたら負けかなと思ってる
As I thought, I can't work with other men
tezukuri no jiman meshi
手作りの自慢飯
All this amazing homemade food
naze ni boro makeyou kappu men! yeah
なぜに ボロ負けよ カップ麺！いえー
Why do I feel defeated by cup noodles! Yeah
sonna koto yori watashi no ai no yukue wa dou na…
そんなことより　 私の愛の行方はどうな…
About that, I wonder where my love went to...
shiranai!
知らないよ !
I don't care!
sake da! onna da! bokuchi da! wasshoi!
酒だ!女だ!博打だ!わっしょい!
Alcohol! Women! Gambling! Cheers!
baka inu ni aho tanukime
バカ犬にアホ狸め
You stupid dog and idiot tanuki
odoru ahou ni miru aho
踊る阿呆に見る阿呆
You dancing fools actually look like fools
onaji aho nara odoranya sonson
同じアホなら踊らにゃそんそん
You're equally a fool if you're dancing
kemo kemo kemo kemo kemoke
ケモケモケモ けもけもけ
ossan nii-san nee-san minasama rasshai!
おっさんにーさんねーさんみなさまらっしゃい！
Old man, brother, sister, everybody come on!
chintonshan! binchoutan!
ちんとんしゃん！ びんちょうたん！
tonshan
とんしゃん！
choutan!
ちょうたん！
tarira tarirarira dance! dance! dance!
タリラタリラリラ　ダンス！ダンス！ダンス！
yoisho!
よいしょ！
heave-ho!
kemo kemo kemo kemo kemoke
ケモケモケモ　けもけもけ
kokuri kokuri burning heart
コクリコクリ　バーニングハート
hanchahan isshohan
半チャーハン 一升半
Half fried rice! Half a bushel!
say say
シェイシェイ
Say, say!
yeah yeah
いえーいえー
Yeah, yeah!
gugure! kukure! gugure!
繰繰れ！繰繰れ！繰繰れ！
Gugure! Kukure! Gugure!
rereru rerure LOVE★
れれる　れるれー LOVE★
Rereru rerure LOVE★
It doesn't feel like the new year
until your first shrine visit.
Is that right?
Yeah.
Hey, what did you guys wish for?
To eat as many cup noodles as possible.
To be lovey-dovey with my darling!
Money!
I'd like a cute doll!
Tama?
I want to learn more about
Earth... about this world!
Urgh, Yamamoto-kun?
Um, I'd like a handsome young boy, an angelic
young boy, and a little rosy-cheeked boyfriend!
Tengu! Don't wish for little boys
at the start of the new year!
I'm wishing for them precisely
because it's the new year!
Shut up!
F-Friends!
You're all a bunch of boors!
Didn't anyone else make the same wish I did?!
The 108 worldly desires erased by the
New Year's bell returned just as quickly.
And a new year of Kokkuri-san's stressful life
with Kohina and the gang has begun.
The beginning of a new year...