Inugami-san, I see you're in
your female form today.
As I told you before, my sex hasn't
been settled yet, so if you wish...
I can take my male form...
Or my animal form.
Whatever you desire.
My darling, I want you to be my soeur.
How do you do, Onee-sama?
Our household has a one-child policy.
Go back to your den, you mongrel!
Your house! Your house!
If it frustrates you so, Fox-dono,
you could become a woman, too.
I won't become a woman.
Hey, I'm back.
She's beautiful. There's a real beauty here.
Faster than the speed of light, he was behind her.
Fox, why were you hiding this beauty from me?
Uh, that's Inugami.
Tch...
He will revert to his male form soon.
That doesn't matter!
The person in front of me right
now is a beautiful woman.
The past and the future aren't important!
The present is everything!
Inugami, run!
Hey, now, don't talk like I'm some savage beast.
That's just mean.
It's not like I'm going to eat her.
Come to think of it,
we haven't spoken much before.
This is a good opportunity, little lady.
Why don't we head over to my bed and—
And have something to eat and drink
while we get to know each other?
What were you starting to say?
I won't do anything to you.
My body and soul belong to Kohina-sama.
I would never waste my time on a mere tanuki.
Perhaps you should take a look in
the mirror and cool your head.
Please don't use me as a shield
while you hurl insults at him.
Women are so cute when they hide
behind someone while acting tough.
I like strong-willed girls.
He's unfazed!
Little lady, I'll give you some money,
so let's... get something to... to eat...
The morals of my household
are becoming corrupted.
This isn't good for Kohina's upbringing.
Hey, Shigaraki.
Stop hitting on people in my house.
It's not good for Kohina's upbringing,
and I prohibit indecent behaviour.
You're right.
Then you don't mind if I go
out hunting for girls, right?
That's the same thing!
Whimper, whimper!
My darling, Shigaraki-dono is giving me filthy looks!
I'm scared of that tanuki!
My darling...
You mongrel!
The morals of my household...
hanchahan isshohan
半チャーハン 一升半
Half fried rice! Half a bushel!
say say
シェイシェイ
Say, say!
yeah yeah
いえーいえー
Yeah, yeah!
gugure! kukure! gugure
繰繰れ！繰繰れ！繰繰れ！
Gugure! Kukure! Gugure!
rereru rerure LOVE★
れれる　れるれー LOVE★
Rereru rerure LOVE★
hi fu mi ah
ひーふーみー 鳴呼
One, two, three, ah!
oh yeah get down boogie
おーいえー　げっだーん　ぶーーぎーー
Oh yeah get down boogie
dance dance dance
だんす　だんす　だんす
Dance, dance, dance
kokon touzai shinkyuu you hou
古今東西　新旧洋邦
All ages past and present, here and across the ocean
ryouri ga dekiru otoko wa moterunda!
料理ができる　男はモテるんだー !
The men should be able to cook!
de? sorede?
で？それで？
And? What of it?
souji mo kanpeki! sentaku mo kanpeki!
掃除も完璧! 洗濯も完璧
Perfect cleaning! Perfect laundry!
airon mo osaihou mo
アイロンも お裁縫も
Ironing and sewing too
ooi shouchu to tako wa sa
おーい焼酎とたこわさー
Hey, get the alcohol and snacks!
jichikai ni mo deterundaze?
自治会にも出てるんだぜ?
How about joining the neighbourhood council too?
go kinjo tsukiai perfect
ご近所付き合いパーフェクト
My relationship with our neighbours is perfect
ha ha
はっは
nanoni nande tei hyouka!
なのに なんで低評価!
And yet why aren't I appreciated?!
hatarake subete wa waga kimi no tame ni
はたらけ全てはわが君のために
Work! It's all for my darling!
subete wa ore no niito seikatsu no tame ni
全ては俺のニート生活のために
It's all for my life as a NEET!
kao wa ii hou darou
顔はいい方だろ
My face looks good, right?
zannen
残念!
Too bad!
kirei na kamishitsu darou
きれいな髪質だろ
My hair is beautiful, right?
shiruga!
白髪!
It's grey!
suiji sentaku wa makasero
炊事洗濯はまかせろ
You can leave the cooking and cleaning to me
okan!
おかん!
Mother!
kamenokou yori toshinokou daro!!
亀の甲より年の功だろ ! !
The older the wiser, right?!
gakugaku iwasezu ni utatte kudasai
ガクガク言わずに歌ってください
Please sing without being outspoken
hai! hai! hai! hai!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
kemo kemo kemo kemoke
ケモケモケモ けもけもけ
ossan nii-san nee-san minasama rasshai!
おっさんにーさんねーさんみなさまらっしゃい！
Old man, brother, sister, everybody come on!
chintonshan! binchoutan!
ちんとんしゃん！びんちょうたん！
tonshan
とんしゃん！
choutan!
ちょうたん！
tarira tarirarira dance! dance! dance!
タリラタリラリラ　ダンス！ダンス！ダンス！
yoisho!
よいしょ！
Heave-ho!
kemo kemo kemo kemo kemoke
ケモケモケモ　けもけもけ
kokuri kokuri burning heart
コクリコクリ　バーニングハート
hanchahan isshohan
半チャーハン 一升半
Half fried rice! Half a bushel!
say say
シェイシェイ
Say, say!
yeah yeah
いえーいえー
Yeah, yeah!
gugure! kukure! gugure!
繰繰れ！繰繰れ！繰繰れ！
Gugure! Kukure! Gugure!
rereru rerure LOVE★
れれる　れるれー LOVE★
Rereru rerure LOVE★
Doki Fansubs | http://doki.co | http://anidex.moe
Haunting 5
"The Flowers on the Desk are a Message!"
Fox Udon
Every morning, a vase of flowers is
placed on Ichimatsu Kohina's desk.
Ichimatsu has no friends.
She doesn't give it much thought herself,
but she is not a victim of extreme
bullying. She is simply a loner.
Loners don't bother them,
but this is what most of her
classmates think of her.
Likes cup noodles
Delusional
Weird girl
Don't care
Don't want to associate with her
Has bobbed hair
Don't like her
She's the contractor of darkness
I fought with in a past life, right?
Other
Likes cup noodles
She was scolded by Kokkuri-san for having
"lacks a cooperative attitude" written
in her correspondence notebook.
Enduring Three-Hour Lecture
School is a place to learn
about human relationships...
Could you stop looking so grim?
The presence of the vase someone always
places there has become natural,
and no longer fazes her at all.
At first, Ichimatsu was curious about the vase.
The vase wasn't like being insulted in passing.
On every school day, fresh flowers were
put in the vase before she arrived.
How diligent.
On rainy, windy, and even snowy days,
someone would come earlier than everyone
else to place new flowers in the vase.
Occasionally, the person responsible for
the flowers would observe Ichimatsu.
I gave her fresh and beautiful
flowers again today! I'm so cruel!
It must have wounded her pretty deeply today!
Is she hurt?
Is that a somewhat sad expression? No...
She's so shocked, she's expressionless!
Yes, that must be it!
The complete lack of response seems
to destroy the culprit's confidence.
Sometimes, the vase would capture
the attention of new teachers.
Ichimatsu-san, are you being bullied?
I'm not sure.
Doesn't having this vase here upset you?
The vase doesn't bother me,
but the aphids on the flowers do.
Be sadder, darn it!
A normal person would lament being bullied
by having a vase placed on her desk!
"Little Bully Girl"
You're an abnormal bob-cut girl!
The vase... Bullying...
Could it be...
Are you the person who has been
decorating my desk with seasonal flowers?
That's right! Tremble in fear!
You're the one who put the vase on her desk?
Yes, that's right!
Come with me to the faculty office.
No! No, no, no!
There is safety in silence.
I hope Kohina's getting along with her classmates.
If you're so worried about her, go check on her.
Kohina got angry when I went
to check on her every day.
So even the girl doesn't like
overprotective parenting, eh?
You should quit drinking all day and do some work!
The Black Ships arrive in the Sea of Japan
I am working.
How is that working?!
Because of you, I got in big trouble!
How dare you tattle on me, you coward?!
Didn't you cause your own downfall?
Grr! I'll never forgive you!
Calm down, um...
(Bully)
Jimeko-san.
Don't give me a weird nickname!
But I don't know your name, Jimeko-san.
You don't remember?!
I sat next to you all last year...
We were in the same class...
Let's see...
Suzuki... No, Sato-san?
No.
Don't just list common names
if you don't know what it is.
She's got a lot of nerve for a victim of bullying.
If you're too impertinent,
I'll give you more and prettier flowers!
I'll increase the bouquet size by 20%!
How is that a threat?
It'll put a strain on my allowance!
You're threatening yourself?
So you bought those flowers with your own money.
That's right! It's really hard on me!
I refrain from buying things I want and having fun,
and I help out at home every day to boost
my allowance so I can buy those flowers!
All so I can bully you!
Why don't you try living
for yourself a little more?
How dare you act so unconcerned when
I'm working so hard to bully you?!
How frustrating!
Was it a lot of work?
Yes!
I never let the rain, wind, snow,
or summer heat stop me.
I even came in during typhoons.
Even when I was sick with the
flu, I never missed a day!
You should take better care of yourself.
If it's so difficult, why don't you stop?
No. My parents told me to
never leave things unfinished!
Can't you direct that ambition
toward something else?
You just want me to stop
bullying you, don't you?
I see right through you!
No. It doesn't particularly distress me,
so I don't mind either way.
No emotional damage?
Only your wallet has experienced damage.
Jimeko-san, why do you bully me?
Huh?
Do you not like me?
What? Uh...
I-It's, um... well...
I-I'll be mean and not tell you!
She blushed and ran away.
It started a year ago.
Transfer Student
She's a transfer student.
Everyone be nice to her.
Jimeko-san was determined
to make new friends.
I hope I make a lot of friends.
You're the transfer student. Nice to meet you.
Don't get the wrong idea!
I don't want to be your friend or anything!
Transfer student?
However, because of her "shy tsundere"
personality, she failed to make friends.
I failed spectacularly from the get-go.
My last hope of making a friend
is the loner who sits next to me...
Pant
But it's hard to just talk
to her out of the blue.
Pant
I need an excuse to talk to her...
I know! I'll drop my eraser
and get her to pick it up!
Pant
Toss.
You dropped this.
She didn't notice.
One more try?
But she didn't notice.
Surely she'll notice this and talk to me!
She noticed, but she did not speak to her.
I was so shocked she hit me,
I lost my chance to talk her.
I'll have to create another
reason for her to talk to me.
The plan to accidentally hit her with a ball,
apologize, and then become friends.
Oh, no! My hand slipped!
Cup Noodles
The plan to have her show
concern after seeing her trip.
Even though she tried many things,
she never caught her attention.
The transfer student is amazing!
She's tough. Too tough.
This stone-faced girl only
opens her heart to cup noodles.
What a terrifying girl!
If it's come to this, I'll do whatever it takes!
I'll do anything to get her attention!
Take this!
And so, having lost sight of her original
goal, Jimeko-san became a bully.
The Next Day
There are flowers here again today.
Everyone knows about the spiteful
vase put on her desk every day.
Today's flowers are Japanese magnolias.
In the language of flowers, the magnolia means...
It means friendship.
What was it?
They're not very common, so I don't know.
I don't know, either.
It's friendship!
To this day, no one has noticed the
messages hidden in the flowers every day.
Did you hear? There's a new
transfer student coming today.
Really? I wonder if it's a boy or a girl.
Friendship
Apparently, it's a super cool boy.
For real?
A transfer student...
That is not relevant to me.
Take your seats, everyone.
Today, I have a new friend to introduce to you.
Yes, heartless dolls are
unmoved by handsome boys.
Transfer Student
This is Kokkuri-kun.
He's an adult!
Transfer Student
Nice to meet you.
In spite of herself, the doll gave a classic reaction.
You can sit... hmm...
There's a free seat next to Ichimatsu.
There they are... My eyes...
Kokkuri-san!
Salt
Please leave!!
Please leave!
No one summoned you, spirit. Leave.
You didn't have to use rock salt!
Are you trying to kill me?
Then, I will use normal salt instead.
I am kind.
Your kindness stings!
Please leave.
Stop with the salt! Violence is wrong!
Whisper, whisper. Mumble, mumble.
Attacking me with words is even worse.
Ichimatsu, don't tease the transfer student!
Teacher, you are being deceived by an evil fox.
There you go again.
Be nice to the transfer student.
You got in trouble.
Stupid dog of the educational institution.
How were you able to get into school?
Where's the paperwork?
Oh, that?
Kokkuri-kun is a teenage shota
I turned a leaf into my paperwork.
That's a crime.
As a fox, I have to trick people sometimes.
Want me to trick you, too?
Kokkuri-san.
Can you turn leaves into money?
That's a crime.
A numberless 500 yen coin...
No.
I just wanted to ask.
Dolls do not use much money.
You hardly have any possessions, either.
So...
Can you turn leaves into cup noodles?
You'll get a stomachache.
Look, it's just an illusion.
I only make it look like something else.
I can't turn it into anything
more or less than a leaf.
You can't eat it.
I understand. They are actually leaves.
So how upset would my stomach get?
You actually plan to eat it...
Leaf Ramen
When Ichimatsu returned from the restroom...
Kokkuri-san was surrounded by girls.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Maybe I'll volunteer.
Kohina.
I'm saved. You're finally back.
Such slender hips!
Kokkuri-san, are you meant
to be a handsome character?
Yeah. What did you think I was?
It's Ichimatsu-san!
Kohina-sama, if the fox can
become a normal student,
I can start to attend school, too, right?
Inugami! You're inside her backpack today?
I am Kohina-sama's shadow.
I was hiding in here so I could fill
Kohina-sama's salt jar with rock salt!
Sharp
That was you?!
My darling, I shall join this school, too.
Very well.
Hold on! You threw rock salt at me.
Why is it okay for him to come to school?
Nothing I say to Inugami-san will do any good.
Besides...
Bad Luck
I got new rock salt.
It's a bribe!
Don't give her rock salt...
The Next Day
My name is Inugami.
Inugami-kun
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Be nice to him, everyone.
He's an adult!
Inugami-kun
Inugami-san joined the school, too.
You can sit...
I would like to sit next to Kohina-sama.
Kokkuri and Yamamoto are already
sitting next to Ichimatsu.
That's too bad.
Nice to meet you, Yamamoto-kun...
And goodbye.
Hey, Yamamoto. Switch seats with him.
Dog < Cat
Cat > Monkey
I can't see...
Okay, I can see now.
Kokkuri-san, are you nearsighted?
No, it's...
I can't see things close to me.
You're farsighted?
Stare...
Come to think of it, you don't
have animal ears at school.
Of course not.
If people found out I'm an animal spirit,
I wouldn't be able to attend school anymore.
Inugami-kun suddenly became a girl?
Ah, no...
This is just how I am!
What?
She's acting defiant!
She has things that look like
ears on the top of her head!
Oh, these?
They moved!
You're mistaken. These aren't like ears at all.
What? How are you going
to fool them now, Inugami?
These are, in fact, dog ears!
At least try to fool them!
Fox Fire!
She suddenly started burning!
I managed to fool them with a scientific
case of spontaneous combustion.
Either way, it's an unnatural phenomenon.
Fox-dono, don't you think
you're worrying too much?
No one in this scientific
world believes spirits exist.
All mysteries can pass for magic tricks.
You should worry more!
Also, your guns won't pass for tricks.
If you don't want to be discovered,
you could become a doll, too.
What? But then I couldn't make friends.
Kokkuri-san, did you come to school
because you wanted friends?
No, not for me.
Ow!
I wanted to make friends for you.
They say your friend's friends
are your own friends.
If I make friends, you'll have more friends.
Though you probably don't care...
Kokkuri-san.
There's no way they're our age.
That's against the Swords
and Firearms Control Law.
Why do beautiful people only hang around her?
Yikes... Apparently, hanging out with
Ichimatsu makes you catch fire.
I feel the distance between me and my
classmates has grown since you came.
That's impossible!
Also, I believe your friend's
friends are only acquaintances.
Only the distance between Kokkuri-san
and the female classmates narrowed.
oboete iru kana
覚えているかな
I wonder if you remember
ichiban kanashii toki
一番悲しい時
Your saddest moment
yokei na kotoba wo
余計な言葉を
Needless words
minna sutete kureta
みんな捨ててくれた
Have been cast aside
karappo no ude ni
空っぽの腕に
Wrapped under my arms
sotto mogurikonde
そっと潜り込んで
I've been crouching down
sameta jounetsu
冷めた情熱
The cooled down passion
atatame nagara
温めながら
Starts to warm up again
taisetsu na mono ga
大切なものが
What's precious to me
koko ni hitotsu dake
ここにひとつだけ
There is only one thing
arifureta hibi ni
ありふれた日々に
In these mundane days
shizuka ni nagareru merodi
静かに流れるメロディ
A melody is quietly passing through
issho ni utawanakute mo ii kara
一緒に歌わなくてもいいから
We don't need to sing together
kono mama tenpo ni makasete hoshii
このままテンポに任せて欲しい
I want to leave it to our current tempo
mawaru mawatte
回る　回って
It goes around and around
hikari no naka de
光の中で
Inside the light
mawaru mawatte
回る　回って
It goes around and around
kurikaeshite
繰り返して
Over and over again
Next Time
Haunting 6               Kohina, the Cyclops, and Shigaraki!
This Week's Fluff: Nacchan
Today's fluff is a parakeet, huh?
I wonder if you can cuddle birds...
Fox-dono, do you prefer sauce or salt?
Wait, what are you talking about?!