Tonight, some shady men are taking care of some business.
It's a simple yet dangerous, hard-boiled night,
where dangerous goods and large sums of money change hands.
We kept you waiting.
You're quite late, Coccurino.
My apologies, Inugami.
My partner is so hot-headed, he ended up in a fight.
Hot-headed, huh?
There was just a cute kitten I tried to get closer to.
You shut up!
In reality, these two were police
investigators infiltrating mafia dealings.
Detective Coccurino
Detective Shigaracci
Can they handle this without revealing their true identity?
Let's get started with the transaction.
Show what you've got.
Here.
Certainly.
How about you show yours, too?
The goods.
Very well.
These are...
Just cup noodles?
Our famiglia uses top quality cup noodles.
These are top quality cup noodles, sourced by my darling herself.
However, we have something else top quality in store for you.
Top quality bullets!
We've been surrounded!
We know you're police spies,
Detective Coccurino, Detective Shigaracci.
How did you find out?
Your partner told the lady at the bar
he'll be doing an infiltration operation.
What are you doing?!
It's a top secret operation!
The ladies really started to bite when I said it's a secret operation...
All the attention got me happy, so...!
And that's why we'll get turned into swiss cheese!
Consider the consequences!
Unfortunately for you, all these cup noodles belong to me.
I will mark your graves with empty cup noodle cups.
As expected from my darling!
What a wonderful one-liner!
Damn it!
Nothing has gone according to plan since I paired up with you!
I could say the same!
This strangely dressed odd pair of detectives...
is surely causing another incident somewhere as we speak.
"Mafia Without a Code?"