Sweets
Selection
Valentine's Day, huh?
That's right, it's February 14, Valentine's Day.
The day women give chocolate to men.
Kohina is not going to give me any chocolate, is she?
Kokkuri-san.
It's chocolate.
What? You're giving it to me?
Do you want it?
Yeah!
But you're not getting it!
Damn you!
It's Valentine's!
What bullying is this?!
Stop teasing me and give me some!
Ichimatsu only gives chocolate to others when we're stranded on a snowy mountain.
Doesn't your heart tell you to share delicious things with others?
Ichimatsu is a doll without a heart.
You devil, making me happy when I had already given up...
Chocolate, I want chocolate!
Kokkuri-san, chocolate.
Kohina?
Open wide.
What a shame.
It was just an afterimage.
Damn you!
It was a fake offer!
If it's come to this...
I'll take it with force!
She beat me...
Whoops, got my Valentine's chocolate!
But little girl, don't ruin your food.
If it falls down, you can't eat it, right?
It's all right.
It's safe if you pick it up within three seconds.
That's out.
Oji-san, here's your Valentine's chocolate.
Oh! Are you okay giving it to someone like me?
What, wait a minute!
Why is he getting any while I'm not?
What?
Because this is chocolate I prepared in advance for her to give to me now.
For holding onto his chocolate for a while, I was promised half of it.
Even the line I should say when giving it was predetermined.
If anything, this is me giving her chocolate.
Is that not pointless?
Well, when I say I prepared it, I mean I exchanged the 10,000 yen I won at pachinko for chocolate.
Since there's a lot, I though we'd have fun eating it.
I'll even give some to you.
Getting it from an old man doesn't make me happy at all.
Aren't you an old man, too?
I'm still young and full of energy!
"Young and full of energy" smells like an old man's despair.
But that's rare, you winning when gambling.
How much did you spend?
A hundred thousand!
So you just blew ninety thousand?!
Old man Shigaraki is as good-for-nothing as always.
But even if it was agreed upon beforehand,
him getting chocolate from Kohina made Kokkuri-san a little envious.
"Valentine's Kokkuri-san!"