One evening, during dinner...
Kohina, how was school today?
Did you have fun?
Same as always.
Kokkuri-san is worried about Kohina, so he often asks her such questions.
There isn't even a single interesting thing.
For a doll without a heart, interesting things do not exist.
Ichimatsu is a doll that works as programmed.
You sound more like a robot than a doll.
What is it?
You go there even though it's not interesting?
It doesn't matter whether school is interesting or boring.
You must attend school.
Even if you're bored, you have to attend.
Even if you're bored, you have to work.
You're kind of intense today...
And even though a lot of things are boring, you have to live.
Don't say things are boring!
You make them interesting yourself!
Work is part of life, too!
So you go have a grand old time at the employment office.
That's boring, so no.
Time to sleep.
My darling!
I wonder if Kohina is getting bullied because she's like that.
No idea.
Something has disappeared again.
Kokkuri-san's worry was spot on.
Someone stole it to bully you?
I might just have dropped them somewhere.
Dropped?!
I picked something up on the stairs earlier.
Could it be...
Dreams
Is this what you dropped?
It's not anything that abstract.
Dreams
My gym uniform is missing.
It was here just a moment ago.
So someone is bullying you.
No, I'm sure...
It's a divine sign telling me to skip gym class!
Positive
So it wasn't someone's ill will towards you?
That's right.
The victim decides whether it's bullying or not.
Ichimatsu doesn't mind things which are convenient for her.
Bullying means attacking with cup noodles.
I'll put these out of Kohina's reach so she won't eat them.
An example of bullying for her
My books have disappeared, too.
I can't attend today's lesson like this.
What a wicked prank.
Siesta = A noon-afternoon break
Guess I have no choice but to have a siesta in the nurse's office.
Seriously, what a mean prank.
Don't skip class!
In the end, the the teacher lent her the books.
So we managed to finish another meaningless day.
Nice decadence!
What happened today was nothing special for a doll girl.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
But if Kokkuri-san knew, he'd be worried.
How was it today?
Same as always.
Is that so?
By replying with "same as always", she keeps it a secret.
Next
Day
My slippers are missing today.
A serial thief...
Some people are just terrible.
The lost things were the doing of a stalker.
"Secret Kohina-chan!"