It's the day Inugami-san transferred to Kohina's school.
It's already this late?!
Huh?
It's barely 07:00.
Gosh.
Mama, why didn't you wake me up?
Who're you calling "Mama"?!
Why are you being so disgusting early in the morning...
Oh, no!
I'm gonna be late! I'm off!
What just happened?
Talk to us...
That's a heroine who bumps into you on the day she transfers in, and you get a glimpse of her panties.
No! Where are you looking, you pervert?!
How cliched.
And why a heroine?!
It appears the goal is to raise shoujo manga flags.
How can you exorcise that demon?
Speed: 80 km/h!
He's running like a girl, but he's still so fast! Too fast!
You'd die if she crashes into you!
Dodge, Kohina!
No, I won't make it!
The flag gets raised!
Doll...
When you thought it was too late...
...power!
Ichimatsu dodged with all her strength.
Where are you looking, you pervert?!
Inugami-san would cause a big ruckus at school later,
but here she was still just wearing girls' clothes.
Also, Kokkuri-san didn't know yet that this was his last time going to school.
"The morning Inugami-san transfers in!"