Red.
Every time I think of you,
the leaves turn red.
hanchahan isshohan
半チャーハン 一升半
Half fried rice! Half a bushel!
say say
シェイシェイ
Say, say!
yeah yeah
いえーいえー
Yeah, yeah!
gugure! kukure! gugure
繰繰れ！繰繰れ！繰繰れ！
Gugure! Kukure! Gugure!
rereru rerure LOVE★
れれる　れるれー LOVE★
Rereru rerure LOVE★
hi fu mi ah
ひーふーみー 鳴呼
One, two, three, ah!
oh yeah get down boogie
おーいえー　げっだーん　ぶーーぎーー
Oh yeah get down boogie
dance dance dance
だんす　だんす　だんす
Dance, dance, dance
kokon touzai shinkyuu you hou
古今東西　新旧洋邦
All ages past and present, here and across the ocean
ryouri ga dekiru otoko wa moterunda!
料理ができる　男はモテるんだー !
The men should be able to cook!
de? sorede?
で？それで？
And? What of it?
souji mo kanpeki! sentaku mo kanpeki!
掃除も完璧! 洗濯も完璧
Perfect cleaning! Perfect laundry!
airon mo osaihou mo
アイロンも お裁縫も
Ironing and sewing too
ooi shouchu to tako wa sa
おーい焼酎とたこわさー
Hey, get the alcohol and snacks!
jichikai ni mo deterundaze?
自治会にも出てるんだぜ?
How about joining the neighbourhood council too?
go kinjo tsukiai perfect
ご近所付き合いパーフェクト
My relationship with our neighbours is perfect
ha ha
はっは
nanoni nande tei hyouka!
なのに なんで低評価!
And yet why aren't I appreciated?!
hatarake subete wa waga kimi no tame ni
はたらけ全てはわが君のために
Work! It's all for my darling!
subete wa ore no niito seikatsu no tame ni
全ては俺のニート生活のために
It's all for my life as a NEET!
kao wa ii hou darou
顔はいい方だろ
My face looks good, right?
zannen
残念!
Too bad!
kirei na kamishitsu darou
きれいな髪質だろ
My hair is beautiful, right?
shiruga!
白髪!
It's grey!
suiji sentaku wa makasero
炊事洗濯はまかせろ
You can leave the cooking and cleaning to me
okan!
おかん!
Mother!
kamenokou yori toshinokou daro!!
亀の甲より年の功だろ ! !
The older the wiser, right?!
gakugaku iwasezu ni utatte kudasai
ガクガク言わずに歌ってください
Please sing without being outspoken
hai! hai! hai! hai!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
kemo kemo kemo kemoke
ケモケモケモ けもけもけ
ossan nii-san nee-san minasama rasshai!
おっさんにーさんねーさんみなさまらっしゃい！
Old man, brother, sister, everybody come on!
chintonshan! binchoutan!
ちんとんしゃん！びんちょうたん！
tonshan
とんしゃん！
choutan!
ちょうたん！
tarira tarirarira dance! dance! dance!
タリラタリラリラ　ダンス！ダンス！ダンス！
yoisho!
よいしょ！
Heave-ho!
kemo kemo kemo kemo kemoke
ケモケモケモ　けもけもけ
kokuri kokuri burning heart
コクリコクリ　バーニングハート
hanchahan isshohan
半チャーハン 一升半
Half fried rice! Half a bushel!
say say
シェイシェイ
Say, say!
yeah yeah
いえーいえー
Yeah, yeah!
gugure! kukure! gugure!
繰繰れ！繰繰れ！繰繰れ！
Gugure! Kukure! Gugure!
rereru rerure LOVE★
れれる　れるれー LOVE★
Rereru rerure LOVE★
Doki Fansubs | http://doki.co | http://anidex.moe
Haunting 10
"Kureha's Days Spent Waiting in Vain!"
It's a red leaf.
Beware of Bears!!
And in the middle of winter. How unusual.
Adults who wear nothing but a bell in
the middle of winter are unusual, too.
Leave me alone!
Don't make me sound like an exhibitionist!
Anyway, where did this red leaf come from?
Sniff, sniff.
I can smell a maple tree over there.
Let's go check it out.
Don't leave without saying anything
just because you don't want to go!
Only the leaves of this tree are red.
It's as if it's only autumn right here.
The red leaves sure are beautiful.
Why do leaves turn red?
Is there a corpse underneath the tree?
Don't be so ominous!
Also, that was a cherry tree!
The leaves must be sipping enough
lifeblood to replace their green
with this complementary red hue.
Like Elizabeth Bathory.
Don't dig under it to find out!
Maybe this tree was late
turning to autumn colours.
No.
This maple tree's leaves are red all
year long, regardless of the season.
Oh?
This woman...
What an unusual maple tree.
And who might you be?
Me?
I am...
I'm waiting here for someone.
I promised to meet someone important here.
She must be...
I've waited in vain all this time.
If he couldn't make it...
He could have at least sent a smoke signal.
What era were you born in?
What are you doing this deep in the mountains?
Ta-da!
We've been walking for hours to catch the sale
at the supermarket past the mountains.
They've got great bargains!
Cup noodles are five yen off.
They're the sort of people who'd climb mountains to save money regardless of transportation costs!
It's strange that this tree's
leaves are red all year long.
Do you know why?
Then...
If someone suddenly asked you why
monkeys' bottoms are always red,
could you give an answer?
If you don't know, just say so!
By the way, monkeys have red bottoms
because their blood is visible through the skin.
Do you know or don't you?!
"Because it's a mysterious
maple tree" is my final answer.
I'm disappointed.
I thought the person I was
waiting for had finally come,
but it was just some cosplayer with a little girl.
I'm not cosplaying!
What? Then are you wearing
animal ears to be fashionable?
I'm the real Kokkuri-san!
That's why I look like this!
I see. I'm sure that's what you think.
I'm not pretending!
Look. I'm the real deal.
Kon, kon.
How does that work? Where's the switch?
Where's the battery?
Hey, s-stop!
He is not battery-operated.
Don't!
I-I'm not...
She mistook him for a toy.
Hey! Stop!
You said you thought
someone had finally come.
Have you been waiting alone in
these cold mountains all this time?
Yes. I've been waiting forever.
Through spring...
summer...
fall...
and winter.
I practically live here.
Wow. She's patient.
I would have left after three minutes.
You eat cup noodles in three minutes when
they're meant to stand for five, don't you?
What kind of person are you waiting for?
Is it a handsome prince?
Why are you sweating?
I've been waiting so long,
I don't remember what he looks like.
If you've forgotten that, just go home.
Kokkuri-san, the sale is starting.
Oh, right.
We're gonna get going.
Wait!
If you're heading into town, could you find
the person I'm waiting for and bring him here?
I'm unable to leave this place,
for certain reasons.
Please.
What should we do?
Rice Coupon 10kg
I'll give you two months' worth of rice coupons.
Leave it to me!
Saving money, saving money!
Use this drawing to help you.
I drew it long ago, so I'm sure it's accurate.
You didn't beautify him, did you?
No.
Okay, we're off.
Oh, but you haven't told us your name yet.
My name?
Kureha.
It's written as "red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha.
It's written as red leaves"
and pronounced "Kureha."
Kureha, huh?
Those out-of-season bright red leaves...
And a girl whose name is written as
"red leaves" standing under that maple tree.
"Kureha"
It fits too well to be a coincidence.
Most likely...
Kureha is the spirit of the maple tree.
Please refrain from discussing the
supernatural while we're in town.
It's like all the pieces have fallen into place.
If Kureha is the spirit of the tree,
that explains everything.
She can't go far from the tree
because she is its spirit.
The maple tree's leaves are red
because it's possessed by a spirit.
I accepted 500 yen to listen to your
babble, but it's just too boring!
What? When did you get here?!
Kitty, kitty.
She's playing with a cat over there...
It's so fluffy.
So fluffy.
Don't meow at me.
How will we find the person she's waiting for?
I'm not sure.
What's this?
It's so-and-so and such-and-such,
and such-and-such and so-and-so.
Then, such-and-such and so-and-so.
Oh, really?
I'm amazed you understood that.
I have no idea what she said.
Leave it to me.
Just ask a mountain god. They know
everything that happens in the mountains.
Tengu
Tengu!
This man, huh?
"Mountain God
Tengu"
Yeah, I know him.
Really?
Yes.
Where is he?
I won't tell you for free.
How much will it cost?
Three.
For three photos of handsome
young boys, I'll help you.
I don't have any!
Pant
I don't want any of those
phony child idols, either.
Pant
I prefer pure amateurs.
Boys' choirs are okay, though.
Pant
Don't make such specific requests
without the slightest shame, you g*y pedo!
Pant
Tengu-san likes young boys.
It's the official Japanese standard
for tengus to like little boys!
What's wrong with liking boys?!
Don't get defiant!
You pervert!
Shut up, you lolicon jerk!
Pervert!
Shut up, lolicon!
Stop this pointless fighting.
Stay out of this, you loli!
A
Tengu-san likes young boys
Twitch
It's said that dolls are unperturbed.
If you don't have any photos, take some.
Can't you transform into
anything, even a little boy?
Ack!
Let me do it!
Taking pictures of an old man dressed
up to look young feels so pointless.
Then don't take them!
But I accept your payment.
I will tell you.
The person you're looking for
died long ago.
What?
It happened decades ago.
The girl waiting for him
also died long ago.
She's a ghost bound to that tree,
waiting for a man who will never come.
How sad it is.
What? A bound ghost?!
Kokkuri-san's guess was way off the mark.
Damn.
I was wrong. How embarrassing!
I'd better make sure Kohina doesn't tell.
Kureha is the spirit of the maple tree.
It's like all the pieces have come together.
She's got dirt on me!
Was their promise so important that
she was bound to that tree after death?
It happens all the time.
A childhood friend heads off to war and
never comes back as he promised to.
It's straight out of a cheap novel.
I understand she has regrets,
but she should forget about that
promise and move on to the afterlife.
Speaking of the afterlife,
I hope I'm reborn as a little boy
so I can play with other boys...
Keep your pedophilia in check!
I promise I'll come back. Wait for me.
I'll come home as quickly as I can.
Your name will be the first
one I call when I return,
Kureha.
Liar...
She probably knows the man is dead.
I wish I could help her reach
the afterlife, but it's tough.
All I can do is give people information
and hit on young boys.
You're good for nothing.
Just die already.
A bound ghost, huh?
Bound...
"Ground"
Change the way she's "bound,"
and you've got an adult B-movie.
"Bondage"
You must not let your libido soar
on wings of imagination.
Anyway...
B-Bringing him back is... mission impossible...
You know... I knew. I knew all along...
Y-Yeah... So you don't have
to wait for him anymore.
You can cross-
I knew.
But I kept waiting.
I can't cross over to the afterlife now!
Hey... Hey...
The stress built up inside of her exploded.
I couldn't give up on my own.
I thought I could if someone
else made me face the truth.
But I can't give up, after all.
Good grief. I don't like hearing girls cry.
I'll call him.
What?
You can do that?
I'm a priest, you know.
Invoking spirits is my speciality.
I'm actually not supposed to meddle
with the other side too much,
but a man who isn't moved by a
woman's tears is no man at all.
I'll show you what it really means to
invoke a spirit, and not as child's play.
Hello?
Could you connect me to the Hirasaka Underworld?
Did he dial 104?
Did he dial
Directory Assistance?
I'll get his spirit delivered right away.
Delivery service?
Oh, hello. I'd like to get something delivered.
What? My name? Identification?
My name is Shigaraki-
Click
They hung up on me when I told them my name.
What did you do?
He's blacklisted by every industry
for being a professional bilker.
I wish I could try again,
but I don't have the strength.
I can't connect to the other side anymore.
Sorry I couldn't help you, miss.
It's fine.
Connecting to the underworld
must be spiritually exhausting.
Remaining Funds: 0 Yen
No. I have a prepaid phone.
The strength he lacked was financial strength.
A
Doesn't have the financial strength
I will lend you my phone.
Thank you.
Hello, this is Ki**taku.
Don't pretend to be someone else!
Give me that. I'll do the talking.
Sorry to bother you while you're so busy.
We worked together while I was a
contractor at the Uka-no-Mitama Company.
Yes. Yes.
I'd like to check your inventory of spirits.
Yes. That's correct.
Kokkuri-san's maturity saved the day.
Yes. Yes.
Goodbye.
Okay. I understand.
You honest citizen...
What did you find out?
Can you invoke his spirit?
Kureha, I have good news and bad news.
Which do you want first?
What?
The bad news first, I guess.
The bad news, huh?
Your boyfriend's spirit can't be invoked.
After he died, he didn't wait for you.
He was asked to be
reincarnated immediately.
The good news is that you
don't have to wait anymore.
That's good news?
Yes.
The person you promised to meet
came to you a long time ago.
Your boyfriend chose to be reborn
as a maple tree for some reason.
Your name will be the first
one I call when I return,
Kureha.
Red. Every time I think of
you, the leaves turn red.
What a patient couple.
So there really are matches made in heaven.
Why do I seem to attract nothing but losers?
Meanwhile, it might have
slipped your mind by now, but...
Inugami-san, having run away from home,
was talking to Yamamoto-kun.
Don't be stubborn. You should go home.
I don't want to.
I won't go home until they come get me!
After that, he wandered around aimlessly.
He saw many things and encountered
many strange places and people.
How small my world is.
All my concerns are no more
than "every little thing."
And his mental maturity grew a great deal.
No, they are "every little Kohina!"
E.L.K! E.L.K!
Every little thought is for Kohina-sama!
His mental maturity... grew a great deal?
Why was I being so stubborn?
Having a home to return
to is a wonderful thing.
I shall return to Kohina-sama.
Hot! Hot, hot, hot!
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
oboete iru kana
覚えているかな
I wonder if you remember
ichiban kanashii toki
一番悲しい時
Your saddest moment
yokei na kotoba wo
余計な言葉を
Needless words
minna sutete kureta
みんな捨ててくれた
Have been cast aside
karappo no ude ni
空っぽの腕に
Wrapped under my arms
sotto mogurikonde
そっと潜り込んで
I've been crouching down
sameta jounetsu
冷めた情熱
The cooled down passion
atatame nagara
温めながら
Starts to warm up again
taisetsu na mono ga
大切なものが
What's precious to me
koko ni hitotsu dake
ここにひとつだけ
There is only one thing
arifureta hibi ni
ありふれた日々に
In these mundane days
shizuka ni nagareru merodi
静かに流れるメロディ
A melody is quietly passing through
issho ni utawanakute mo ii kara
一緒に歌わなくてもいいから
We don't need to sing together
kono mama tenpo ni makasete hoshii
このままテンポに任せて欲しい
I want to leave it to our current tempo
mawaru mawatte
回る　回って
It goes around and around
hikari no naka de
光の中で
Inside the light
mawaru mawatte
回る　回って
It goes around and around
kurikaeshite
繰り返して
Over and over again
The leaves are still red.
That's love.
"Burned Up Badly in the Atmosphere"
There are still unsolved mysteries
surrounding this tree.
What?
Normally, plants use the chlorophyll in their
green leaves to photosynthesise nutrients.
Photosynthesis!
Chlorophyll
Let's photo-
synthesise.
But...
These red leaves lack chlorophyll.
This tree should be dead.
Don't insert biology into fantasy!
Honestly, it's exhausting.
What?
I knew it.
You can talk?!
Next Time
Haunting 11           Adult Dropout Cosplay!
This Week's Fluff: Shirayuki-kun
It's another rabbit.
It looks like the other rabbit.
This one has dark rings around its eyes, too.
It looks so soft!