Welcome home!
As usual, Kokkuri-san greets Ichimatsu like a mother when she gets home.
How was it?
Was school fun today?
Did you make any friends?
Kokkuri-san often asks questions like this,
but today he was somehow different...
It's too bright.
What's wrong, Kohina?
You're pointlessly radiant today, and it's bothering me.
Please stop it.
Huh?
Don't say that.
Aren't I completely glittering, glowing and cool today?
Inugami-san, let's go on a walk.
It's my turn today, and if I skip it,
Kokkuri-san won't buy cup noodles for me.
I have to go on a walk with you, even if I don't want to.
Inugami
Inugami-san appears to be out, so we can't go on a walk today.
There's no helping it.
My darling!
I am here.
It is extremely rare that I wouldn't be within 15 metres of you.
Do not worry.
I would prefer it if you stayed more than 15 metres away from me whenever possible.
You're being a tsundere, which are so popular these days?
You say the opposite of what you truly think.
It's okay.
I can hear the true voice of your heart. I understand.
Starting tomorrow, I will make sure to stay within 15 metres of you!
Both Kokkuri-san and Inugami-san are pointlessly radiant and weird today.
Sometimes they tighten their drooping faces, trying to show you how cool they are.
I am neither particularly impressed by handsome men nor jokesters.
That's probably true.
But it seems they try to be as handsome as they can be.
Sometimes you just want to put effort into something, right?
I don't really understand.
You know, even I...
...am putting in the effort to not lose to them.
Yes!
"I am handsome", is what they thought.
But their confidence got shattered by Ichimatsu.
"The Exciting?? Ichimatsu Family?"