It's been two or three days now, and I still
don't know how to get back to normal.
I think you're fine the way you are.
Anyway, pour me another.
Didn't you say you'd stop drinking and smoking?
This? This isn't sake.
Don't lie to me! You're wasted!
It's the companion of any man on
a liquor ban: ethanol disinfectant.
Disinfectant
Don't drink pure alcohol!
And that's the ethanol I use for cleaning!
Spit it out! Spit it back into my bottle!
Damn you...
Kokkuri-san.
I discovered a scroll regarding
your curse in the storage shed
that can only be opened by those who are cursed.
Well done!
You should be grateful to my darling.
All right. Now I can go back to-
You've got to be kidding...
What does it say, fox?
hanchahan isshohan
半チャーハン 一升半
Half fried rice! Half a bushel!
say say
シェイシェイ
Say, say!
yeah yeah
いえーいえー
Yeah, yeah!
gugure! kukure! gugure
繰繰れ！繰繰れ！繰繰れ！
Gugure! Kukure! Gugure!
rereru rerure LOVE★
れれる　れるれー LOVE★
Rereru rerure LOVE★
hi fu mi ah
ひーふーみー 鳴呼
One, two, three, ah!
oh yeah get down boogie
おーいえー　げっだーん　ぶーーぎーー
Oh yeah get down boogie
dance dance dance
だんす　だんす　だんす
Dance, dance, dance
kokon touzai shinkyuu you hou
古今東西　新旧洋邦
All ages past and present, here and across the ocean
ryouri ga dekiru otoko wa moterunda!
料理ができる　男はモテるんだー !
The men should be able to cook!
de? sorede?
で？それで？
And? What of it?
souji mo kanpeki! sentaku mo kanpeki!
掃除も完璧! 洗濯も完璧
Perfect cleaning! Perfect laundry!
airon mo osaihou mo
アイロンも お裁縫も
Ironing and sewing too
ooi shouchu to tako wa sa
おーい焼酎とたこわさー
Hey, get the alcohol and snacks!
jichikai ni mo deterundaze?
自治会にも出てるんだぜ?
How about joining the neighbourhood council too?
go kinjo tsukiai perfect
ご近所付き合いパーフェクト
My relationship with our neighbours is perfect
ha ha
はっは
nanoni nande tei hyouka!
なのに なんで低評価!
And yet why aren't I appreciated?!
hatarake subete wa waga kimi no tame ni
はたらけ全てはわが君のために
Work! It's all for my darling!
subete wa ore no niito seikatsu no tame ni
全ては俺のニート生活のために
It's all for my life as a NEET!
kao wa ii hou darou
顔はいい方だろ
My face looks good, right?
zannen
残念!
Too bad!
kirei na kamishitsu darou
きれいな髪質だろ
My hair is beautiful, right?
shiruga!
白髪!
It's grey!
suiji sentaku wa makasero
炊事洗濯はまかせろ
You can leave the cooking and cleaning to me
okan!
おかん!
Mother!
kamenokou yori toshinokou daro!!
亀の甲より年の功だろ ! !
The older the wiser, right?!
gakugaku iwasezu ni utatte kudasai
ガクガク言わずに歌ってください
Please sing without being outspoken
hai! hai! hai! hai!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
kemo kemo kemo kemoke
ケモケモケモ けもけもけ
ossan nii-san nee-san minasama rasshai!
おっさんにーさんねーさんみなさまらっしゃい！
Old man, brother, sister, everybody come on!
chintonshan! binchoutan!
ちんとんしゃん！びんちょうたん！
tonshan
とんしゃん！
choutan!
ちょうたん！
tarira tarirarira dance! dance! dance!
タリラタリラリラ　ダンス！ダンス！ダンス！
yoisho!
よいしょ！
Heave-ho!
kemo kemo kemo kemo kemoke
ケモケモケモ　けもけもけ
kokuri kokuri burning heart
コクリコクリ　バーニングハート
hanchahan isshohan
半チャーハン 一升半
Half fried rice! Half a bushel!
say say
シェイシェイ
Say, say!
yeah yeah
いえーいえー
Yeah, yeah!
gugure! kukure! gugure!
繰繰れ！繰繰れ！繰繰れ！
Gugure! Kukure! Gugure!
rereru rerure LOVE★
れれる　れるれー LOVE★
Rereru rerure LOVE★
Doki Fansubs | http://doki.co | http://anidex.moe
Haunting 8
"Kokkuri-san's Steamy Secret Hot Spring Tour!"
No...
Did you find anything useful?
I'm going to go search for the philosopher's stone.
He pretended he never read it.
Gloom
Hey, what did the scroll say?
Give up. You'll be that way
for the rest of your life.
I guess I'll just kill myself.
F-Fox!
Taking a bath calmed me down some.
He stabbed me.
There was an interruption, though.
How did you find taking
a bath in a woman's body?
Did you enjoy yourself, sir?
Huh? I've been bathing every
day since I became a woman.
Besides, I'm already used
to seeing the female body.
Are you bragging about how popular you are?
Were you just bragging about how popular you are?!
Don't put it like that!
It's because I used to transform!
Come to think of it,
women put all kinds of stuff on their
faces when they get out of the bath.
Why don't you do the same?
What?
I'm a man! Why would I copy what women do?
I'll always be a man!
I'll do what I always do!
Even now that he's a woman, nothing
about his lifestyle seems out of place.
It's too late once it gets rough!
Collagen
You're so middle-aged.
A skin care regimen including
lotion, cream, and eye cream
was already part of his daily routine.
Hey, fox!
I won a hot springs trip in a lottery!
Hot Springs Trip Ticket
That sounds great. I like hot springs.
Do you want to come with me?
Yeah.
We leave tomorrow morning
and we'll stay overnight.
Make sure you're ready.
Okay.
They're going on a date.
And they're staying overnight.
What?!
Curses. He tricked me.
I let my guard down because we used to go drinking together and go on trips with the seniors' club!
Kokkuri-san, you're a
member of a seniors' club?
I would imagine he gets on well with them.
Then maybe he invited you on this
trip with the same intentions.
You think so? Maybe you're right.
I'm being overly self-conscious, aren't I?
By the way, the old man used most of
his allowance to buy those tickets.
It's a date...
He's happily packing.
That makes it hard to turn him down.
Shigaraki, if this is a date, I don't think I can...
It's not a date. Don't worry.
Really?
Will you come if I say that?
Which is it?!
Well, it wouldn't be any fun if I forced you to go.
Fine, then. I give up.
Hey, the fox isn't coming.
Why don't the three of us go?
What?
Let's enjoy the hot springs together
and get some good food in us.
Hot springs with Kohina-sama!
I would like to try the local cup noodles.
Okay, okay. Leave it to me.
It's too bad, really.
There's rumoured to be a hot spring that
counteracts curses in that resort town.
Is that true?
Yeah.
Then I'll go!
Kokkuri-san, did you actually intend to go?
So this is it, huh?
I like how subdued it is.
The place has heart, doesn't it?
It's deep in the mountains.
Frankly, it looks like quite a desolate town.
Are we nearly there yet?
I want to jump in those warm
hot springs as soon as possible.
It's bold of you to complain after you
forced your way along with us.
The doggie will be our pet!
I, the hot springs enthusiast, will be
the fourth member of your party!
Well, I couldn't just sit idly by when you
said you were going to the hot springs.
Anyway, where's this legendary hot spring?
Where's the hot spring
that will remove my curse?
Now, calm down.
We've got our bags with us. Let's check in first.
Yeah, I guess.
Let's go to our lodging!
Welcome, Ichimatsu-sama's party of four.
Yamamoto-kun, what a coincidence.
E.T.
What is Yamamoto-kun doing here?
Yamamoto-kun, who resembles an
alien, is Kohina's classmate.
It's a coincidence that they ran into him,
but Kokkuri-san doesn't like him very much.
Is he your friend, little girl?
I have no friends.
He is Kokkuri-san's friend.
What? Yamamoto-kun is my friend?
Give me a break. I don't even like him.
The Fool's Room
Hm...
I suppose this room's all right...
You dare say that after you forced
your way along with us?
Okay, let's go check out the hot springs!
Shigaraki! Is this inn's hot spring
the one that removes curses?
Nope. It's just a normal hot spring.
It's good for stiff shoulders,
back pain, and your skin.
Skin!
What?
Where is it, then?
Calm down.
It's rumoured to be somewhere
in this hot spring town,
but it's nearly time for dinner.
Let's look for it after we've eaten.
I'm hungry.
You idiot! Why do you think I came he-
Fine.
But we're definitely going
to look for it after dinner.
Okay, okay.
We still have some time. Why don't
you go take a bath with the girls?
Okay, fine.
Good for the skin, huh?
Maybe I'll take a bath, too.
Fox-dono, hurry! Hurry up!
Large Bath
Men's Bath
Women's Bath
You don't belong in here!
I feel rejuvenated.
This is paradise.
Stare.
I will make cup noodles using this water.
You'll make yourself sick. Don't.
How cruel of you to leave me behind, Fox-dono.
Shut up! It's your fault you got stuck to a pillar.
Why are you suddenly in your woman form, anyway?
There's nothing wrong with girls
spending a little time together naked.
Come, my darling! Let us wash every
nook and cranny of each other's bodies!
Get out of here, you pervert!
Don't lead Kohina down some weird path!
That was a nice bath.
Meanwhile, in the men's bath,
Shigaraki was, predictably,
searching for a hole to peep through.
Anyway, Fox-dono, you have
quite the lewd body, meow.
Hey! Stop that!
Don't touch me!
So incredibly bouncy!
They bounce like a teenager's do!
And they're giant, like softballs!
Amazing! So amazing!
I wish you'd share them with me!
Stop!
The way you unscrupulously show
off your femininity is disgusting.
Hey! Don't touch my butt!
I can't take it anymore!
I can't take it! I can't take it! I can't take it!
I can't take it any-
What? Why are you wearing bikinis?
It's a countermeasure against
peeping tanuki perverts.
Well, I guess this is pretty nice, too.
Quit peeping into the women's bath!
Yeah!
Die, scum.
Kokkuri-san, you seem like you
would be more popular as a woman.
Why do you dislike transforming into one?
I can do housework, and I'm attractive.
When I'm a woman, men swarm around
me and ask me to marry them.
That's why I don't want to be a...
E.T.
The Fool's Room
Time to eat.
What a spread.
All right! Liquor!
It all looks delicious.
I can't move.
Thank you for the meal.
I'm stuffed.
And I didn't have to lift a finger.
Now that we're done eating, let's go find
the legendary curse-removing hot spring!
I'm going to visit the hot spring here again.
Fine. I'll go by myself.
I'm going outside for a smoke.
It's snowing.
Do you know where the
curse-removing hot spring is?
Apparently, there are a few
places that might be it.
I just noticed...
A
Normal
He's matching his stride with mine!
He's treating me like a woman!
How dare he mock me?!
I won't let you match my
stride so easily, damn tanuki!
Are we playing tag?
Wait up, you!
It's not tag, you idiot!
Quit treating me like a woman! I don't like it!
Well, sure, if you insist...
I won't treat you like a woman.
Don't stand between me and the road!
Secret Bath Echo Bath
Secret Bath
Panda Bath
Removes curses that
turn you into a panda!
Legendary Secret Bath
Removes curses that turn you into a woman!
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
Legendary Secret Bath
Effects: Removes curses that turn you into a woman
* Does not work on older women
How dare you get my hopes up?!
No luck...
Is there really no way for me to turn back?
Shooting Gallery
This brings back memories.
A shooting gallery, huh?
This might make you feel better.
Here.
Whoa...
All right. Let's do this!
Let me see that.
I'm a pro, you know.
I used to run a shooting gallery myself.
They seem fine for now.
If Kokkuri-san is in danger of
being attacked, I will do this.
I'll book you a hospital appointment.
Give me your stuff.
No chance. I'll carry my own stuff.
Don't treat me like a woman.
Don't be like that. You're
swaying all over the place.
Giving girls attention is what I live for.
I can't treat you like a woman
once you're back to normal.
At least let me have this.
Give up. You'll be that way
for the rest of your life.
I'll never get back to normal.
What?
I'll be a woman for the rest of my life.
Good news for you, huh? You can
shower me with attention forever.
H-Hooray.
But I don't want your attention!
Th-That's too bad.
I'll get these bags home in a flash!
No need for you! How do you like that?!
Don't rest every five metres.
Let me carry them. This is taking too long.
Ow!
I'm not into pain, you know.
I don't like leaving others to do things
I should be able to handle myself.
At the very least, I want to carry my own bags.
I want to be a man for as long as I live.
You're such a pain.
If you want to carry them that badly,
carry them all by yourself.
Do as you please.
I'll do as I please, too.
It's fine. You can carry your bags yourself.
What?
If you're collapsing under
the weight of your burdens,
I'll prop you and your burdens up.
You're not just propping me up! You're carrying me!
P-Put me down! Don't treat me like a woman!
Shut up!
Fox, whether your friend is a man or a woman,
when they're in trouble, the human
thing to do is extend a helping hand.
Did you know? The character for "person"
Person
isn't two people supporting each other.
It's one person standing alone,
unsupported by anyone else.
That's the worst piece of trivia
you could have shared right now!
People are born alone and die alone.
But there isn't a single person who
can keep standing alone forever.
You need the strength to ask
for help when you need it.
Things will work out with you
turning back into a man, too.
Don't worry about it.
Things'll work out?!
Don't say irresponsible things like that
just because it's not your problem!
Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm saying I'll help you.
Of course...
By that, I mean I'll make you stop
wanting to become a man again.
Huh? Wha-
In that moment, the curse was
broken by a kiss from a prince.
Bleeeeuuurgh
The magic of their love is gone, too.
Why did you have to turn back now?!
They're soiled! You soiled my angel lips!
What the hell?! You're the one who kissed me!
You're the filthy one, damn it!
Shut up!
You idiot! After all I did for you!
How tragic.
Shut up!
Damn you for turning back into a man!
The curse of the Ichimatsu family, whose
motto is "make them suffer again and again,"
is a brutal curse that causes one to return to
normal when they have a touching moment
with a member of the opposite sex.
Next Time
Haunting 9              The Age of Many Worries!
This Week's Fluff: Miku-chan
This one's a doggie, too.
It seems to be enjoying its walk.
I find it a hassle to go on walks.
My darling!