There's nobody here.
Even though I have some business with Kokkuri-san.
Even though he's always so clingy it's irritating,
he's not here when I have business with him.
Kokkuri-san is so ill-timed.
Inugami-san and old man Shigaraki, too...
It's unusual that nobody is around.
Calico Cat-san, are you friends with
White Cat-san who always comes by?
You're so fluffy and smell of the sun.
What?
Calico Cat-san, you're White Cat-san's mother?
Oh, and the father is Black Cat-san, right?
So that's how it is, Black Cat-san is a good-for-nothing man,
and Calico Cat-san raised White Cat-san as a single parent, right?
How praiseworthy.
Does Black Cat-san frequent pachinko parlours, like our old man Shigaraki?
Little girl, I don't frequent pachinko parlours.
Old man, since when have you been there?
You didn't notice because you were deep in talk with the cat lady.
I didn't actually talk with Calico Cat-san,
but just pretended to talk with the cat,
in a ladylike pretend play typical for girls.
Why? That's a lonely game.
It's not like I am lonely.
I played with Calico Cat-san since nobody was around.
Huh...
It's rare that neither the fox nor Inugami are home.
That is correct.
Are you done with patrolling pachinko parlours for today?
Yeah, I'm all out of money for today.
Right then, I guess I'll have a beer!
Has the fox put any in the fridge?
Is someone a good-for-nothing man if he only goes to pachinko parlours and drinks beer during the day?
The old man is not a good-for-nothing man, but solid garbage.
He's busy patrolling pachinko parlours and checking on horses' conditions.
My darling.
You'll catch a cold if you sleep here.
Inugami-san, is Kokkuri-san home already?
Well, it appears Fox-dono is not here.
Is something the matter?
Just a little something.
Is that so?
Inugami-san, were you out somewhere?
Yes!
I heard there is a bargain for good
coffee beans, so I went to buy them.
I acquired top quality beans!
My darling, how about having a wake-up cup together with me?
I don't drink coffee because it's bitter.
I was going to eat a cup noodle snack.
My darling!
He still isn't back.
Yes
No
Kokkuri-san.
Will Kokkuri-san still not come home?
I'm home.
Kokkuri-san.
Sorry about that!
I went to pick up the knife I had sharpened,
but I got back late because I ended up chatting with someone.
Yes
No
So, did you have some business with me?
Yes.
Let's see...
What, parents' day at school?
Where did you guys appear from?
Earlier, I threw it away without
showing you, and was scolded harshly.
They had me promise this time.
I showed it to you now, so please don't come.
Ah, got it.
Master's parents' day...
Dressed-up young wives and female teachers...!
Several days later
All right, I'll go then!
You're right!
We have to be fast or we'll be late.
And anyway...
What are you wearing, Shigaraki?!
Where do you guys think you're going?
What now?
I have considered the occasion, and so I'm smart in a suit today.
I, too, am wearing a suit I had made for today.
You're always wearing one, aren't you?!
Fox, where do you think you're going, being all fancy in your only good suit?
Fox-dono, were you about to secretly go to my darling's parents' day without us?
Well... I found the printout which was thrown away earlier.
I couldn't go on the day after the parents' day...
So I decided next time I'd go in secret.
So...
So?
So don't get in my way!
I won't let you be the only one!
I won't be left behind either!
In the end, while the police held the
suspicious trio, the parents' day had ended.
But Kokkuri-san's life as an attendant is not over yet!
I'll definitely go to the next parents' day!
"The Day Kokkuri-san Is Not There?"