Drugstore
My regular hair dye is on sale.
You dye your hair?
Only when I'm an animal.
I'm more colourful and cuter
as a blond fox, right?
Artificial cuteness, like pets dyed
in bright colours, disappoints me.
Stab!
Synthetic Colour
Come to think of it, you're two-toned.
Do you dye your hair, too?
No, it's all natural.
I don't dye my hair.
I'm getting old, though.
I put a lot of effort into my hair.
I don't dye my hair.
If I dyed my hair to hide my age
like the fox does, I'd go bald.
Who's going to go bald? That's ridiculous.
A handsome protagonist like
myself could never go-
I-If I put it back within three
seconds, I'm still safe!
No, he's out.
hanchahan isshohan
半チャーハン 一升半
Half fried rice! Half a bushel!
say say
シェイシェイ
Say, say!
yeah yeah
いえーいえー
Yeah, yeah!
gugure! kukure! gugure
繰繰れ！繰繰れ！繰繰れ！
Gugure! Kukure! Gugure!
rereru rerure LOVE★
れれる　れるれー LOVE★
Rereru rerure LOVE★
hi fu mi ah
ひーふーみー 鳴呼
One, two, three, ah!
oh yeah get down boogie
おーいえー　げっだーん　ぶーーぎーー
Oh yeah get down boogie
dance dance dance
だんす　だんす　だんす
Dance, dance, dance
kokon touzai shinkyuu you hou
古今東西　新旧洋邦
All ages past and present, here and across the ocean
ryouri ga dekiru otoko wa moterunda!
料理ができる　男はモテるんだー !
The men should be able to cook!
de? sorede?
で？それで？
And? What of it?
souji mo kanpeki! sentaku mo kanpeki!
掃除も完璧! 洗濯も完璧
Perfect cleaning! Perfect laundry!
airon mo osaihou mo
アイロンも お裁縫も
Ironing and sewing too
ooi shouchu to tako wa sa
おーい焼酎とたこわさー
Hey, get the alcohol and snacks!
jichikai ni mo deterundaze?
自治会にも出てるんだぜ?
How about joining the neighbourhood council too?
go kinjo tsukiai perfect
ご近所付き合いパーフェクト
My relationship with our neighbours is perfect
ha ha
はっは
nanoni nande tei hyouka!
なのに なんで低評価!
And yet why aren't I appreciated?!
hatarake subete wa waga kimi no tame ni
はたらけ全てはわが君のために
Work! It's all for my darling!
subete wa ore no niito seikatsu no tame ni
全ては俺のニート生活のために
It's all for my life as a NEET!
kao wa ii hou darou
顔はいい方だろ
My face looks good, right?
zannen
残念!
Too bad!
kirei na kamishitsu darou
きれいな髪質だろ
My hair is beautiful, right?
shiruga!
白髪!
It's grey!
suiji sentaku wa makasero
炊事洗濯はまかせろ
You can leave the cooking and cleaning to me
okan!
おかん!
Mother!
kamenokou yori toshinokou daro!!
亀の甲より年の功だろ ! !
The older the wiser, right?!
gakugaku iwasezu ni utatte kudasai
ガクガク言わずに歌ってください
Please sing without being outspoken
hai! hai! hai! hai!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
kemo kemo kemo kemoke
ケモケモケモ けもけもけ
ossan nii-san nee-san minasama rasshai!
おっさんにーさんねーさんみなさまらっしゃい！
Old man, brother, sister, everybody come on!
chintonshan! binchoutan!
ちんとんしゃん！びんちょうたん！
tonshan
とんしゃん！
choutan!
ちょうたん！
tarira tarirarira dance! dance! dance!
タリラタリラリラ　ダンス！ダンス！ダンス！
yoisho!
よいしょ！
Heave-ho!
kemo kemo kemo kemo kemoke
ケモケモケモ　けもけもけ
kokuri kokuri burning heart
コクリコクリ　バーニングハート
hanchahan isshohan
半チャーハン 一升半
Half fried rice! Half a bushel!
say say
シェイシェイ
Say, say!
yeah yeah
いえーいえー
Yeah, yeah!
gugure! kukure! gugure!
繰繰れ！繰繰れ！繰繰れ！
Gugure! Kukure! Gugure!
rereru rerure LOVE★
れれる　れるれー LOVE★
Rereru rerure LOVE★
Doki Fansubs | http://doki.co | http://anidex.moe
Haunting 9
"The Age of Many Worries!"
Wait, wait, wait...
Hair's bound to fall out when I'm washing it.
I'm worrying too much.
It's okay. I'm still fluffy-
Look, keseran-pasaran.
You dropped all these keseran-pasaran.
No!
A
Shed
Hair
I shall put them in a jar and nurture them.
Give those back!
Give me back my keseran-pasaran
before the three seconds are up!
The shed hair showed no mercy.
They were like the wings of
angels, signifying the end.
This is bad.
I'm going bald! I'm really going bald!
Clam down... I mean, calm down.
What's wrong with going bald?
That's right. I'm handsome.
Rotten caviar is still caviar!
I'll still be handsome even without my hair.
No. If I rot, I'll just be garbage.
God, why are you testing me so?
If I have to go bald, I want
to look like Sean Co***ry.
No, I should be positive.
I should treasure everything
I'm blessed with now...
So that I don't lose anything else.
I will protect my head
from all sources of stress!!
I will protect my head from
all sources of stress!
Effort
I want to google "hair growth"
and "hair loss prevention,"
but I don't know how to use this...
I don't want to break it like I did before.
Would you like some help?
Yeah, thanks.
But make sure you don't tell
anyone, especially Inugami-
Grin
A certain demon found a nice toy.
Over the Back
Kill before you are killed.
That is the law of survival of the fittest.
Kokkuri-san, do you know
where Inugami-san is?
No, I don't.
"I just thought of a really
funny joke!" thought Ichimatsu.
It's very advanced, though. What shall I do?
...thought Ichimatsu.
But she believed Kokkuri-san would understand.
You have a white hair.
Ow!
Kokkuri-san tried desperately to contain his rage.
Meanwhile, Kohina waited for his response.
Don't discover white hairs
on my already white head!
Ichimatsu thought...
Oh, a white hair.
...that pointing out a white hair on
a naturally white-haired person
was avant-garde and surreal,
and thus totally hilarious,
and took great pride in what
she thought was a great joke.
How funny
Ichimatsu thought that, perhaps, Kokkuri-san
couldn't keep up with her comedy style.
Meanwhile, Kokkuri-san considered
forgiving her if she apologized.
Ichimatsu considered whether or
not she should explain the joke.
She agonized over whether an explanation
would render the joke stale.
Meanwhile, Kokkuri-san wondered,
"Why won't she apologize, god damn it?"
God damn...
I was joking.
What? You were joking?!
Grind
Grown-ups don't understand.
Want some, little girl? Just kidding.
Kokkuri-san was so worried about
his hair that he couldn't sleep.
Worrying will make me go bald.
Worrying will make me go bald...
Kohina, can't you sleep?
You'll turn into Alcindo.
K-Kohina! What did you just say?
Hope
Alcindo? How old are you, anyway? Hey!
It was truly an ill omen.
Hope
Dreams
Effort
It's morning already.
Dreams
Effort
I broke the tanuki's jug.
After getting no sleep,
Kokkuri-san was distracted.
Sorry.
Can't be helped.
They all break eventually.
Just glad you didn't
harm a hair on your head.
"Just glad you don't
have a hair on your head."
Did you say you're glad I'm losing my hair?!
You hit me because you misheard me?!
I'm still fluffy!
What's wrong with him?
Oh, my...
They know!
They definitely know!
You'll turn into Alcindo.
Just glad you don't
have a hair on your head.
The top of my head is experiencing a catastrophe!
A
Scalp Diagram
Blackheads, Grime
Inner Skin
Outer Skin
Sebaceous Gland
Catastrophe
Annihilation of Roots!!
Nothing will grow here anymore.
Drugstore
At this rate, they'll make me their toy
and pull out the rest of my hair.
It's shedding...
Is the stress making it fall out faster?
Damn it! I can't give up!
This much should do it...
I won't go bald...
I won't go bald!
I refuse to go bald!
You idiot!
If you use that much hair tonic now,
you'll end up in a serious mess!
A serious mess!
There's the mess.
Fluff
Huh?
You evolved into a keseran-pasaran.
You're making way too much
fuss over seasonal shedding.
Are you experiencing the onset of dementia?
We must sheer it.
Shut up!
I'm now at an age that my hair
might not grow back anymore!
Also, put those weapons in your hands away!
Kokkuri-san becomes an emotionally
unstable handful during shedding season.
Fluff
Kohina Theatre
One one hand, we have Inugami-san; on the other,
a chrysalis who dreams of becoming a butterfly.
One's all wrapped, while the other's just warped.
Warped
On one hand, we have Shigaraki;
on the other, tap water.
One is colourless, while the other is career-less.
Wait...
Career-less
This last joke must be about me.
On one hand, we have Kokkuri-san...
She couldn't come up with
anything, so she passed on him.
No!
Kohina Theatre Fin
Not "fin"! Not "fin"...
After Kokkuri-san became a giant furball...
You can't be serious! I won't
let you lay a finger on my hair!
You're being absurd.
All your superfluous hair is unsightly.
Don't call it superfluous!
I shall make you cute and stylish.
This is an opportunity for you to change your
image and become popular, like a certain mascot.
Huh? Like that kitty?
Will you really make me fashionable and cute?
Yeah.
We goofed.
Later, Kokkuri-san was hospitalized
for stress-induced gastritis.
Inugami
There's nothing to do.
Inugami Spending Time in His Room (The Dog House)
Maybe I'll go pick on the fox.
Clean, clean, clean.
Cinderella, if you wish to go to the ball,
you must first clean up all this garbage!
Did you come here just to bother me?
The year is almost over.
I don't understand it.
Why doesn't the love between
me and my darling progress?
Because you've only been stalking her.
Do you suppose the attraction is already mutual?
You should do something
about that stalker mentality.
I'm busy right now.
I don't have time to chat with you.
Go away! Go to your house!
My darling, let's go for a walk.
I'm having cup noodles while
Kokkuri-san isn't looking.
House. Go to your house.
Inugami, if you've got nothing
to do, why don't we share a-
I'm not into pain, you know.
The year is almost over.
Before the year ends, I shall make progress
in my relationship with my darling!
Potato Chip Yakisoba
I've been buying nothing but bargain
drugstore and supermarket cup noodles.
I haven't even searched for convenience
store limited edition noodles.
It is an oversight unbecoming
of a cup noodle-ist.
My darling.
I love you.
No matter how many different
limited edition yakisoba flavours I try,
the standard sauce always trumps them.
However, the euphoria of the standard sauce
A
Ignored
can only be recognized once one
has tasted the less common flavours.
A bittersweet confession, like that of an
innocent maiden, didn't seem to work.
Inugami-san doesn't cry, because he is an adult.
My darling won't pay any attention to me.
I'm so bored.
I must do something to capture her attention.
With age comes wisdom.
What? How to make a girl fall in love with you?
Yes.
Put a couple of eye drops in the girl's drink...
How old is that technique?
In your case, if pushing doesn't work,
you may want to try pulling back.
Such conventional advice.
Heave-ho!
It means you're supposed to give her space.
Heave...
Hey!
Inugami left a note.
Huh?
Stare.
My darling.
I am running away. Please don't look for me.
P.S. Do you understand?
Don't look for me.
I mean it, don't.
Inugami.
He ran away because he
wasn't getting any attention.
When he says don't look for him,
he actually wants us to look for him.
Not that I will.
Yeah. He wants us to look for him.
Not that I will, either.
No, wait.
A few things suggest this may not
be an ordinary runaway letter.
Inugami-san's paws don't have fleshy pads,
but there's a paw pad mark here.
This is the work of a third party.
It may be a case of kidnapping.
Not that I'll look for him.
I can't even be bothered to comment.
No one cares about your awful deduction.
Anyway, he's not a child.
He'll come home eventually.
My darling.
Uh, he's waiting for us to come looking for him.
And he's waiting in the yard.
At least leave the house.
You haven't even run away.
I can say one thing with
certainty: he's annoying.
We're wasting time.
It's cold. Let's go inside.
Nobody even cares?
I don't care about anyone but my darling.
I know my darling will come looking for me.
My darling!
Your fiancé is right here.
Please notice me and hold me.
I pray that my obscene desires reach you!
Perception
Oh, no. I forgot to throw out the hot
water for my squid ink yakisoba cup.
In his outrage, Inugami cancelled the
scheduled recording of the afternoon drama
that Kokkuri-san had gotten Ichimatsu to program.
Cry! Scream!
Curse me with your rage!
My darling isn't looking for me.
I already knew, but...
My darling truly doesn't care if I'm not there.
It's quite dark out now.
I dislike the lights inside houses.
Long ago, when I was a stray,
I would gaze at the lights from afar.
I wanted a place to belong inside those lights.
Seems I was only an uninvited guest
trespassing in this house, too.
No one would care if I went missing.
I hate the lights inside houses.
Without you around, we have too much
leftover food that's going to waste.
Let's go home.
I want to go home, too.
My darling...
That's not you!
I'm so sad without you, Inugami-san.
The dog seemed down,
so I tried being nice to him,
but he cried and ran away.
In that situation, I'd run, too.
And so, Inugami-san actually
did run away from home.
oboete iru kana
覚えているかな
I wonder if you remember
ichiban kanashii toki
一番悲しい時
Your saddest moment
yokei na kotoba wo
余計な言葉を
Needless words
minna sutete kureta
みんな捨ててくれた
Have been cast aside
karappo no ude ni
空っぽの腕に
Wrapped under my arms
sotto mogurikonde
そっと潜り込んで
I've been crouching down
sameta jounetsu
冷めた情熱
The cooled down passion
atatame nagara
温めながら
Starts to warm up again
taisetsu na mono ga
大切なものが
What's precious to me
koko ni hitotsu dake
ここにひとつだけ
There is only one thing
arifureta hibi ni
ありふれた日々に
In these mundane days
shizuka ni nagareru merodi
静かに流れるメロディ
A melody is quietly passing through
issho ni utawanakute mo ii kara
一緒に歌わなくてもいいから
We don't need to sing together
kono mama tenpo ni makasete hoshii
このままテンポに任せて欲しい
I want to leave it to our current tempo
mawaru mawatte
回る　回って
It goes around and around
hikari no naka de
光の中で
Inside the light
mawaru mawatte
回る　回って
It goes around and around
kurikaeshite
繰り返して
Over and over again
Next Time
Haunting 10               Waiting in Vain for Autumn Colours!
This Week's Fluff: Yuzu-chan
Today's fluff is a lady cat, huh?
It's female?
Yeah. I could tell right away.
You lewd beast.