I'm Kokkuri-san, the fox ghost.
Summoned by Ichimatsu Kohina,
who calls herself a doll,
I was unable to abandon her after
seeing how unfortunate she was,
and decided to haunt her.
Since Kohina is a loner with no
idea how to take care of herself,
I knew I had to look after her.
That's Kokkuri-san-style justice.
Welcome back.
How was school?
Nothing happened.
What do you want for dinner?
Cup noodles.
No.
hanchahan isshohan
半チャーハン 一升半
Half fried rice! Half a bushel!
say say
シェイシェイ
Say, say!
yeah yeah
いえーいえー
Yeah, yeah!
gugure! kukure! gugure
繰繰れ！繰繰れ！繰繰れ！
Gugure! Kukure! Gugure!
rereru rerure LOVE★
れれる　れるれー LOVE★
Rereru rerure LOVE★
hi fu mi ah
ひーふーみー 鳴呼
One, two, three, ah!
oh yeah get down boogie
おーいえー　げっだーん　ぶーーぎーー
Oh yeah get down boogie
dance dance dance
だんす　だんす　だんす
Dance, dance, dance
kokon touzai shinkyuu you hou
古今東西　新旧洋邦
All ages past and present, here and across the ocean
ryouri ga dekiru otoko wa moterunda!
料理ができる　男はモテるんだー !
The men should be able to cook!
de? sorede?
で？それで？
And? What of it?
souji mo kanpeki! sentaku mo kanpeki!
掃除も完璧! 洗濯も完璧
Perfect cleaning! Perfect laundry!
airon mo osaihou mo
アイロンも お裁縫も
Ironing and sewing too
ooi shouchu to tako wa sa
おーい焼酎とたこわさー
Hey, get the alcohol and snacks!
jichikai ni mo deterundaze?
自治会にも出てるんだぜ?
How about joining the neighbourhood council too?
go kinjo tsukiai perfect
ご近所付き合いパーフェクト
My relationship with our neighbours is perfect
ha ha
はっは
nanoni nande tei hyouka!
なのに なんで低評価!
And yet why aren't I appreciated?!
hatarake subete wa waga kimi no tame ni
はたらけ全てはわが君のために
Work! It's all for my darling!
subete wa ore no niito seikatsu no tame ni
全ては俺のニート生活のために
It's all for my life as a NEET!
kao wa ii hou darou
顔はいい方だろ
My face looks good, right?
zannen
残念!
Too bad!
kirei na kamishitsu darou
きれいな髪質だろ
My hair is beautiful, right?
shiruga!
白髪!
It's grey!
suiji sentaku wa makasero
炊事洗濯はまかせろ
You can leave the cooking and cleaning to me
okan!
おかん!
Mother!
kamenokou yori toshinokou daro!!
亀の甲より年の功だろ ! !
The older the wiser, right?!
gakugaku iwasezu ni utatte kudasai
ガクガク言わずに歌ってください
Please sing without being outspoken
hai! hai! hai! hai!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
kemo kemo kemo kemoke
ケモケモケモ けもけもけ
ossan nii-san nee-san minasama rasshai!
おっさんにーさんねーさんみなさまらっしゃい！
Old man, brother, sister, everybody come on!
chintonshan! binchoutan!
ちんとんしゃん！びんちょうたん！
tonshan
とんしゃん！
choutan!
ちょうたん！
tarira tarirarira dance! dance! dance!
タリラタリラリラ　ダンス！ダンス！ダンス！
yoisho!
よいしょ！
Heave-ho!
kemo kemo kemo kemo kemoke
ケモケモケモ　けもけもけ
kokuri kokuri burning heart
コクリコクリ　バーニングハート
hanchahan isshohan
半チャーハン 一升半
Half fried rice! Half a bushel!
say say
シェイシェイ
Say, say!
yeah yeah
いえーいえー
Yeah, yeah!
gugure! kukure! gugure!
繰繰れ！繰繰れ！繰繰れ！
Gugure! Kukure! Gugure!
rereru rerure LOVE★
れれる　れるれー LOVE★
Rereru rerure LOVE★
Doki Fansubs | http://doki.co | http://anidex.moe
Haunting 2
"A Refreshing Smile is the First Step Towards Becoming a Real Human!"
Hey, Kohina!
Want me to turn you into a real human?
The evil spirit finally shows his true nature...
Uh, that shouldn't have scared you...
I'm worried about you.
I'm concerned you're being bullied
or having sad experiences out there,
or that you'll become incompatible
with the rest of society.
I want you to live a happy life as a real person.
That's why I've decided!
I'll rid your warped mind of those childish
delusions and turn you into a real human!
Out of love!
Dolls seek neither happiness nor unhappiness.
They're bothersome.
What?
You should really drop that doll act.
If you insist on calling yourself a doll, prove it.
If that's the deal, then prove to me
that you're actually Kokkuri-san.
What?
It's practically unnatural how
convenient you are to me.
Can you prove you're not an illusion created
by the warped mind of a lonely girl?
Even your memories may be false
memories implanted in your head.
Perhaps Kokkuri-san doesn't even exist.
You... Wh-What...
I'm right here...
Oh? I don't see anything.
I'm here! I'm right here!
Kohina! Hey! Don't do that!
Stop looking away!
You're making me anxious!
Like fairies, Kokkuri-san disappears
if no one believes in him.
My heart has grown uncertain...
I've had it with dolls...
I succeeded in changing the subject.
Tangerines
Please take in this cute doggie and shower him with love.
Let's at least practice smiling.
You're always expressionless.
A refreshing smile is the first
step towards becoming a real human.
Besides, I want to see your smile.
I don't want to. It's too much trouble.
If that's how you feel, I've got a plan.
Fine. I'll show you the tears of a grown man.
No! No! No! No! No!
No! No! No! No!
"Kokkuri-san Fox Ver."
We have received a complaint
from our neighbours.
I will practice smiling with you,
so please stop crying.
Really?
Yes. In exchange, please let me
touch the pads of your feet later.
You can touch them all you want.
For starters, try copying me.
See?
Smile.
You look like a Fukuwarai face!
I'll try again.
Smile.
Here...
You can touch my paw pads.
Sorry for pushing you so hard...
Kokkuri-san gave up on me.
On closer inspection,
everybody smiles all the time...
I don't understand.
What's so funny?
He's been sitting there this whole time.
Should we report him?
Yeah, we should.
Hey, you!
No one will like you if you look so gloomy!
No one will like me?
Why don't you come play at our arcade?
Smile
Smile.
Western Fashion
If I can't learn to smile properly,
will Kokkuri-san stop liking me, too?
Smile.
Hamburgers
Welcome.
Will you be dining in?
Please give me a smile.
What?
I'd like a smile to go, please.
I-I'm sorry, miss, but we can't box a smile...
In the end, all I got was French fries.
I am addicted to their cheap flavour.
Delicious...
Expressions are nothing more than a
way to visually express one's emotions.
So I should be able to express a
smile using my actions and words.
Kohina, are you on your way home?
Kokkuri-san.
Are you making fun of me?
Taiyaki
I'm surprised you're so
concerned about smiling now.
I thought you'd say,
"Dolls don't smile" and ignore it.
What's gotten into you?
Are you becoming a real human?
No one will like you.
Wh-What is it? Didn't you like my impression?
Forget that I told you to smile.
You're not ready for it yet.
Besides, a smile should happen naturally.
You don't need to force yourself to fit in.
But someone told me that no one
likes children who cannot smile.
What? That's why you're so worried?
I'm not worried.
Wait, did you think I wouldn't like you?
I wouldn't stop liking you over that. Don't worry.
Liar.
You may whisper sweet words now,
but you'll persecute me for being gloomy later.
I won't.
Why are you so mistrustful?
You promise you won't hate me?
I won't.
Do you swear on your life?
I do.
Really, really?
Yeah.
Then, pinky swear it.
If you lie, you have to
swallow a thousand needles.
Ka-pow!
See?! You can do it if you try!
Come on, make that face again!
Come on, smile!
Smile?
No!
Why does that keep happening?
Damn it!
Later, no matter how many times she tried,
her facial features just slid around.
Rain, rain.
Splash, splash.
Kokkuri-san.
Coming to pick me up with an umbrella...
Please take in this cute doggie
and shower him with love
Is it...
an abandoned dog?
Whimper.
What is this?
Whimper...
My darling!
Oh, dear. It was a pervert I shouldn't
have made eye contact with...
He seems to like her.
So, as you can see, a doggie picked me up.
He's a pervert!
It took him only 0.2 seconds to lock the door.
You shouldn't associate with strange
people when you're out!
Let's scatter some salt!
Salt
Here is the salt.
Oh, thanks...
Salt
Yes?
Why are you in here?!
Allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Inugami.
I am a dog ghost.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I have come here because I
wish to haunt Kohina-sama.
Additionally, I picked the lock
on the back door to get in.
Dimple locks are no match for me.
How terrifying!
Are thieves' tricks popular among ghosts?
Kohina-sama, please become my master.
I pledge my loyalty to you for life.
No, thank you!
I have no intention of letting
a dog ghost haunt her!
Is there a problem?
Inugami is the ghost of a dog that was
sacrificed to cast a curse on someone.
Dog
While he brings prosperity to his
master through curses and plundering,
most masters are unable to maintain
Inugami once his power has grown,
Seizure
and they eventually perish.
He pretends to be obedient,
but eventually the beast consumes his master.
He's a dangerous doggie.
Don't worry. I won't let him touch you.
Don't let your guard down.
By the way, Kohina-sama,
anyone who signs a contract with me now
Fox Udon
gets these complimentary cup noodles.
I look forward to working with you!
Kohina!
Dolls are very susceptible to bribes.
A
Loves Cup Noodles
You idiot! Why did you accept his contract?!
You know it's wrong!
The soup bursting with additives
clings to the insubstantial noodles,
spreading its wings inside my mouth and
taking me to the promised land, Arcadia.
It's no use. There's no talking to her!
Our contract has been established.
Gaining favour with young girls is a simple task.
My ambitions will soon come true.
What?
You know Kohina's name and her favourite food.
You're no ordinary Inugami, are you?
Oh, you can tell?
You're right. I am...
Kohina-sama's stalker!
Ugh, that's the worst answer you could have given!
Kohina-sama- No, my darling...
I fell in love with you at first sight!
In my previous life, when I was
actually a dog, I was abandoned.
While others ignored me as
I shivered with uncertainty,
only Kohina-sama stopped to look at me.
She held me.
She showed me warmth.
Ever since you stole my heart that day,
I have always... always been watching you.
What?
I know everything about you.
Your likes and dislikes, your height and
weight, your measurements, your BMI,
your bone density, the number
and locations of your moles,
your genetic makeup... and-
That's creepy!
Now that we have established a
contract, you are as good as mine.
Get away from her!
Now we can nurture our love for
each other under the same roof...
Inugami-san, I love you.
Hurry up and catch me.
I can do it! I can marry Kohina-sama!
I can do it! I can have &#@% with her!
Kohina-sama, I love you!
Yes, I can!
Begone, evil spirit!
Ehral Manufacturing
You damn stalker!
But, Kokkuri-san, aren't you just like him?
I'm not this bad.
I guess he can stay in a private room outside the
house for a while and we'll see how it goes...
Inugami
A private room?
Are you making fun of me?
Kohina made it in art class.
Starting today, I will live here!
Fluffy.
You're fluffy.
They're squishy.
That was a close call earlier.
Murderous intent!
Did we always have this mascot doll?
It's me, Inugami.
Super Cute
Inspired by fancy merchandise, I became
an animal so you would love me more.
Please pet me now.
Squish
He's soft and exquisitely springy.
Not even divine micro-beads or low-rebound
products come close to this feeling.
What an incredible marshmallow body.
What? Does he really feel that nice?
Let me touch...
You bastard!
Kohina-chama.
Write here
How do you write your name, Kohina-chama?
Teach me.
Write here
By changing the manner and tone of his
speech, he tries to appear cuter.
Write here
If you don't write it for me, I'll eat
you, starting with your head.
I'll write it.
Thank you very much.
I'm finished.
Hooray! I'll treasure this for the rest of my life!
What is this?
There are two sheets of paper...
Marriage Registration for the Spirit World
Wife                                                                 Husband
Ichimatsu Kohina                                              Inugami
It was a marriage registration form.
Any last words?
Inugami-san was turned into ground meat.
This hurts.
Shut up!
Is pain the only problem?
You're worried about me?
My darling, you're so kind.
Don't worry. Spirits are quite difficult to kill.
Who are you?
I am your pet, Inugami.
The man became a woman.
I'm not sure what my sex was
before I became a spirit.
Because of that, my sex changes easily.
Both my body and my mind change
to become a man or a woman.
Thus, you can choose the
yuri route or the normal route...
Whichever you prefer.
Additionally, there is no friendship ending.
I have no intention of winning you, Inugami-san.
Kokkuri-san, can you become a woman, as well?
I can become anything.
I want to see what you look like as a girl...
Absolutely not!
Become a woman! Become a woman!
I'll do anything else.
In that case...
Fox Udon
Can you become cup noodles?
You want to eat me?!
Slurp.
My darling, as we're both girls...
As they're both girls, does it make
it okay for them to sleep together?
My darling, I had a scary dream.
Please sleep with me.
Don't lie!
Naturally, they can bathe together, too.
I'll join you.
You know you can't do that!
You idiot!
No! I want to bathe with Kohina-sama!
What is your problem?
How dare you come between me and my darling?
I'll put a curse on you for a
horse to kick you to death.
As Kohina's guardian, I must protect
her from sick perverts like you.
I must calm this situation
as a mascot-type heroine.
It's a cat.
I must innocently make idle conversation.
Cats are very cute.
I am definitely a cat person.
A
Two Canines
Surround him! Surround him!
Show him hell on earth!
You dare lead my master astray, you beast?!
Search for cat and destroy!
Take this, this and this!
Here, take this, and this.
For some reason, they're even
more murderous than before.
Go to hell, felines.
By drowning their sorrows, they seem to
have reached a mutual understanding.
I feel like it's just cats that are popular.
I know.
There's that cat with the ribbon,
and that cat robot thing.
Yeah, really.
All the idols are cats.
When you google cats and
dogs, cats get more hits.
It's unbelievable!
They have a severe inferiority
complex when it comes to cats...
But this makes me realize that
you're actually someone I can talk to.
Same goes for you.
Sorry for turning you into ground meat.
Forget about it.
I'm sorry for everything I did.
No, we were both wrong.
In that case...
Let's shake hands and make up.
You have no intention of making up, do you?
No.
That's not possible.
I don't have the tiniest shred of
intention of making up with you.
I don't need anyone but Kohina-sama.
Don't touch Kohina!
You're a kind of nasty that's
rare in this day and age!
I get that all the time.
By the way, those who associate with me
usually end up with holes in their stomachs.
Just get out of here!
oboete iru kana
覚えているかな
I wonder if you remember
ichiban kanashii toki
一番悲しい時
Your saddest moment
yokei na kotoba wo
余計な言葉を
Needless words
minna sutete kureta
みんな捨ててくれた
Have been cast aside
karappo no ude ni
空っぽの腕に
Wrapped under my arms
sotto mogurikonde
そっと潜り込んで
I've been crouching down
sameta jounetsu
冷めた情熱
The cooled down passion
atatame nagara
温めながら
Starts to warm up again
taisetsu na mono ga
大切なものが
What's precious to me
koko ni hitotsu dake
ここにひとつだけ
There is only one thing
arifureta hibi ni
ありふれた日々に
In these mundane days
shizuka ni nagareru merodi
静かに流れるメロディ
A melody is quietly passing through
issho ni utawanakute mo ii kara
一緒に歌わなくてもいいから
We don't need to sing together
kono mama tenpo ni makasete hoshii
このままテンポに任せて欲しい
I want to leave it to our current tempo
mawaru mawatte
回る　回って
It goes around and around
hikari no naka de
光の中で
Inside the light
mawaru mawatte
回る　回って
It goes around and around
kurikaeshite
繰り返して
Over and over again
Next Time
Haunting 3
Inugami, Stay! Go to Your House!
This Week's Fluff: Torte-kun and Tart-kun
Hey! More cats?!
Are cat people really more common?
Just so you know, foxes are canines!
Fluffy.