What should we have for dinner tonight?
Ah, I'll have to buy that toilet paper that's on sale.
I'll be late! I'll be late!
Huh, Kohina?
What's up?
I'll be late!
Oh, dear!
Hey, wait, Kohina!
What's this outfit?
And where am I anyway?!
I have to hurry!
I won't make it on time!
Ah, Kohina!
What is this place?!
Kohina, where did you go?
And what is this place?
What's wrong?
Why are you so disheartened?
Shigaraki?
Where are you?
Over here.
Hey, Shigaraki, what is this place?
Also, have you seen Kohina?
Miss, my name is not Shigaraki.
As you can see, I'm a Cheshire Cat.
Huh?
Stop messing around!
What are you meowing for, damn tanuki!
What is this place?!
This is Wonderland,
miss Alice.
Wonderland?
And who's Alice-chan?!
I'm Kokkuri-san!
In this world, you're Alice.
Just accept it already.
Huh?!
Well, whatever.
Do you know about Kohina?
If you mean the rabbit lady, leave it to me.
I'll tell you all about her!
Really?
Damn it, doing what the tanuki cat told me...
kinda got me into trouble!
I didn't do anything wrong!
It's that tanuki cat's fault!
It's the truth! Believe me!
Her majesty enters.
Inugami.
What are you doing?
That's creepy!
Off with his head!
Huh?!
What nonsense are you suddenly spouting, you idiot?!
My, you dare talk back to me, the queen?
Take this dirty furball out of here at once!
Shoo, shoo!
Ow, ow, stop this!
I'm not going anywhere!
I made it in time!
My darling!
Kohina!
Just now!
Huh?
I made it in time for cup noodles.
What the heck?!
Huh, it was just a dream?
What a strange dream...
Whoa, it's this late already?
I have to go shopping right away!
Was Wonderland Kokkuri-san's dream or reality?
Right now, Kokkuri-san is more concerned about buying toilet paper on sale.
"Kokkuri-san in Wonderland?"