I am Kokkuri-san, the handsome
spirit haunting Ichimatsu Kohina.
Performing all the household
chores at the Ichimatsu home,
I work day and night to turn
Kohina into a real human.
Beep. Click.
Please replenish energy.
Fill the tank with high octane, please.
It's almost ready.
Similarly, I am Inugami, the super-handsome
dog spirit haunting Kohina-sama.
As my beloved, my sweet honey, my darling,
Kohina-sama's servant, it is my
job to serve as her guard dog...
To bring her the paper every morning...
And...
Ugh.
My, my. There's still so much dust.
...to find fault with Kokkuri-san.
Did you make one less side dish than
yesterday because you're slacking?
To pick on Kokkuri-san.
Don't you think the seasoning's a little bland?
Don't like it? Don't eat it!
No, I shall.
I told you not to put onions in the miso soup!
Do not feed onions to dogs
You're a real pain!
Go eat some Pedigr** dog food!
To pick on him some more.
You're terrible at this.
Can't you fold a single piece of laundry properly?
Don't give me more work to do!
Maybe I should cut my hair soon.
To pick on him all the time.
Long hair hides your wrinkles better.
What?
Stomach Medicine
His plan is to send him
back to the other world.
hanchahan isshohan
半チャーハン 一升半
Half fried rice! Half a bushel!
say say
シェイシェイ
Say, say!
yeah yeah
いえーいえー
Yeah, yeah!
gugure! kukure! gugure
繰繰れ！繰繰れ！繰繰れ！
Gugure! Kukure! Gugure!
rereru rerure LOVE★
れれる　れるれー LOVE★
Rereru rerure LOVE★
hi fu mi ah
ひーふーみー 鳴呼
One, two, three, ah!
oh yeah get down boogie
おーいえー　げっだーん　ぶーーぎーー
Oh yeah get down boogie
dance dance dance
だんす　だんす　だんす
Dance, dance, dance
kokon touzai shinkyuu you hou
古今東西　新旧洋邦
All ages past and present, here and across the ocean
ryouri ga dekiru otoko wa moterunda!
料理ができる　男はモテるんだー !
The men should be able to cook!
de? sorede?
で？それで？
And? What of it?
souji mo kanpeki! sentaku mo kanpeki!
掃除も完璧! 洗濯も完璧
Perfect cleaning! Perfect laundry!
airon mo osaihou mo
アイロンも お裁縫も
Ironing and sewing too
ooi shouchu to tako wa sa
おーい焼酎とたこわさー
Hey, get the alcohol and snacks!
jichikai ni mo deterundaze?
自治会にも出てるんだぜ?
How about joining the neighbourhood council too?
go kinjo tsukiai perfect
ご近所付き合いパーフェクト
My relationship with our neighbours is perfect
ha ha
はっは
nanoni nande tei hyouka!
なのに なんで低評価!
And yet why aren't I appreciated?!
hatarake subete wa waga kimi no tame ni
はたらけ全てはわが君のために
Work! It's all for my darling!
subete wa ore no niito seikatsu no tame ni
全ては俺のニート生活のために
It's all for my life as a NEET!
kao wa ii hou darou
顔はいい方だろ
My face looks good, right?
zannen
残念!
Too bad!
kirei na kamishitsu darou
きれいな髪質だろ
My hair is beautiful, right?
shiruga!
白髪!
It's grey!
suiji sentaku wa makasero
炊事洗濯はまかせろ
You can leave the cooking and cleaning to me
okan!
おかん!
Mother!
kamenokou yori toshinokou daro!!
亀の甲より年の功だろ ! !
The older the wiser, right?!
gakugaku iwasezu ni utatte kudasai
ガクガク言わずに歌ってください
Please sing without being outspoken
hai! hai! hai! hai!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
kemo kemo kemo kemoke
ケモケモケモ けもけもけ
ossan nii-san nee-san minasama rasshai!
おっさんにーさんねーさんみなさまらっしゃい！
Old man, brother, sister, everybody come on!
chintonshan! binchoutan!
ちんとんしゃん！びんちょうたん！
tonshan
とんしゃん！
choutan!
ちょうたん！
tarira tarirarira dance! dance! dance!
タリラタリラリラ　ダンス！ダンス！ダンス！
yoisho!
よいしょ！
Heave-ho!
kemo kemo kemo kemo kemoke
ケモケモケモ　けもけもけ
kokuri kokuri burning heart
コクリコクリ　バーニングハート
hanchahan isshohan
半チャーハン 一升半
Half fried rice! Half a bushel!
say say
シェイシェイ
Say, say!
yeah yeah
いえーいえー
Yeah, yeah!
gugure! kukure! gugure!
繰繰れ！繰繰れ！繰繰れ！
Gugure! Kukure! Gugure!
rereru rerure LOVE★
れれる　れるれー LOVE★
Rereru rerure LOVE★
Doki Fansubs | http://doki.co | http://anidex.moe
Haunting 3
"Inugami, Stay! Go to Your House!"
So fluffy, so fluffy.
You mongrel. I'll never forgive you for
putting your paws all over my darling.
Bring it on!
Inugami-san, stay. Go to your house.
As you wish.
My house is within your arms.
He interprets her commands
in whatever way he pleases.
Do you want me to bury you, you pedo?
Inugami! Dinner.
Hey, Inugami.
Huh? You don't want any?
You don't want to eat, huh?
Inuga-
What's with this space?
Are you surprised?
Using my powers, I've converted
this space into a one-bedroom house.
No, that's not why I'm surprised.
I can't believe you have all these...
I made them all myself.
Don't touch my Kohina-sama
with your filthy hands!
While I was at it, I also made a doll
of you to help me relieve stress.
Don't do that!
Hey, are you...
not wearing any clothing?
Correct.
I am completely naked, but what of it?
This is my room.
Why? Put some clothes on!
Have you no shame?!
What if Kohina came in here?
I'm not in my underwear,
so it's not embarrassing!
This is more embarrassing!
Fox-dono.
Don't you agree that forcing a pet dog to
wear clothes is egotistical and abusive?
Please give it some thought.
Shut up! Put on some clothes!
Inugami-san's words and actions are troubling.
He doesn't obey your commands, either.
Indeed.
Inugami-san's ears only register
things he wants to hear.
Let's play.
As you wish, my darling.
Inugami-san, you need to calm down.
What? What did you just say?
Calm down...
What?
We have no choice but to reform Inugami-san.
Can you do that?
I have a plan.
The other day...
Used Bookstore
I heard someone calling me to a used
bookstore on the outskirts of town.
Come here...
This way...
I was pulled into the store, where I found a book
containing the secret to controlling Inugami-san.
Th-This is...
And you can fix Inugami with that?
Yes.
As long as I have this book, it is possible.
Think Like a Dog Monthly
Dog Training
That's just a dog training book!
It was a bargain at 100 yen.
I thought it would work on Inugami-san, too.
There's no way it would!
He has human intelligence, so it'd
be mean to treat him like that.
But Inugami-san is a dog wearing
the skin of a gentleman.
When he is alone...
He howls when he hears sirens.
He plays with my shoes and even
with the sandals of his nemesis, you.
A
He seems to enjoy
chewing the straps
A
He seems to enjoy
chewing the straps
A
He seems to enjoy
chewing the straps
A
He seems to enjoy
chewing the straps
A
He seems to enjoy
chewing the straps
A
He seems to enjoy
chewing the straps
A
He seems to enjoy
chewing the straps
A
He seems to enjoy
chewing the straps
A
He seems to enjoy
chewing the straps
A
He seemed to be having fun
burying something in the yard.
A
Kokkuri-san's sandals lie here
He looked exactly like a doggie.
Don't just watch him! Stop him!
Don't bother. It won't work.
I feel like it will work.
You think you can treat me like
an ordinary dog, and even train me?
Unbelievable.
This is what happens to dogs who don't listen.
Please stop, my darling! No!
What... an exciting prospect!
And so, Inugami-san's training began.
Inugami-san, shake.
You're not whipping me yet?
Do you want me to hit you?
"It is absolutely necessary to walk a
dog twice a day to relieve its stress."
I see...
I'm going to the supermarket.
If I take him for walks, he should be
reborn as a beautiful Inugami-san.
From now on, we'll go on walks every day.
Kohina-sama...
Walks with Kohina-sama...
It's like a dream!
I feel as though I could be kind to someone now.
The Next Day
There.
Please take me on walks forever.
Three Days Later
I knew. I knew this would happen.
Children tire of things so quickly.
In the end, they always force their
mothers to take care of their dogs.
Hey, why are you in human form?
To irritate you. What of it?
Inugami-san ran out of steam again.
The moon is so bright tonight, I cannot sleep.
My darling, when you cannot sleep,
you should count not sheep, but Inugamis.
I see...
One Inugami-san...
Two Inugami-sans.
Three Inugami-sans.
Four...
Five.
Six, seven, eight, nine...
Another freak...
I wonder if Kohina's asleep.
Why does she pretend to be a doll, anyway?
I am a doll... a doll... a doll...
Doll... doll... doll...
There's nothing wrong with being a little
different, as long as Kohina's happy.
The only thing that worries me is...
Kohina, are you awake?
There's something I want to tell you.
When you're unhappy, don't pretend you're a doll.
When you feel that way,
it's okay to ask for help and cry.
Kohina-sama.
I am a doll. I am a doll.
My darling.
I am a doll.
Punish me. Please punish me, Kohina-sama.
Okay, that's enough, Inugami.
I am a doll.
Let us become one, Kohina-sama.
You are me, and I am you.
I am a doll.
Don't absorb her into yourself!
I told you to stop it!
Go back to your planet!
Oh, nooooo!
I am a doll.
I am-
Kokkuri-san punished the Inugami-sans
by sending them to the moon.
When Kokkuri-san goes shopping and I am
home alone, I secretly eat cup noodles.
Fried Soba Noodles
My Salt
I am very naughty.
As I please... as I desire...
Boiling Water Pilder, on!
Thank you for the-
I'm home.
Absolutely not!
Argh...
Gah!
Okay, okay. You can eat it.
I know you love instant fried soba.
Instant fried soba is not fried soba.
"Since you don't even fry it, shouldn't
it be called boiled-in-a-cup soba?"
...is what everyone always asks.
Still, I find its spirit, to class itself
as fried soba, endearing regardless.
I feel it is sympathetic to my identity.
Its cheapness is irresistible.
The same goes for the crab meat.
It's crab-less crab meat.
It's just boiled fish paste.
It may look like crab, but it can never be crab.
It is imitation crab.
However, the crab meat cannot go
on living as boiled fish paste.
Don't a large number of people become
impostors in an attempt to become
something greater than themselves?
Perhaps I am instant fried soba, as well.
What should I do?
This got heavy and I don't know what to say.
Isn't there something I can do
about her love for cup noodles?
It's not good for her to eat too many of them.
I have a brilliant idea.
You should give her lots of cup noodles.
By continuously giving her cup noodles,
you will make her full and
she'll grow sick of eating them.
I get it!
And then,
you must continue feeding them
to her until she is traumatized.
Bleurgh.
I could never do something that cruel to her!
I want to see my darling in that state!
You're a demon!
Fox-dono, why do you worry
about Kohina-sama so much?
Huh?
I've been wondering it for a while,
but why are you haunting my darling?
You've got a loli-
No! Don't assume I'm like you!
My motives are purer.
It's like... you know...
When you have a long conversation
with the clerk at the register,
because you have no one else to talk to.
What are you, an old man living alone?
Then, when a line forms,
you gaze at the flustered clerk.
You have good taste.
No!
In any case, I don't care about you.
Goodbye.
Then don't ask!
My reason, huh?
Because I made a promise...
She's probably forgotten, though.
Kohina, how much of the past do you remember?
The past...
What did we have for dinner tonight?
Your memory can't be that terrible!
Sometimes, Kokkuri-san wonders if he
should stop haunting Ichimatsu because
of how extremely pitiable she is.
Ache Ache Ache
Kokkuri-san's stomach hurts from
stressing out over Inugami-san.
Ache Ache Ache
My stomach's been hurting
since Inugami showed up.
Inuda Stomach Medicine
Damn you, Inugami! You'll pay for this!
What is Kokkuri-san doing?
His fluff is falling out due to stress?
Whew!
Kohina was pretty nice to me today.
Let me massage your scalp.
Huh?
What's this?
What's Inugami secretly burying?
Is it my sandals again?
Dig here!
I found something.
Handsome Man Monthly
10 Rules for
Becoming Popular
This magazine is for desperate people!
You want me to be nice to Fox-dono?
If you don't, his fluff will fall out.
His fluff?
All his roots will die.
Will you be nice to him?
That's a difficult request.
I am not familiar with kindness.
I was abandoned soon after I was born.
I've only taken things and
had things taken from me.
The only kindness I know is what you showed me.
If you want me to be kind, you must teach me.
That is the training I want you to give me,
my darling.
I love-
"The first rule to becoming popular:
If you want to be popular, play the
beautiful man with a dark past."
"Play"?
Inugami, did you know?
There are such interesting magazines in this world.
Like this reference magazine you dropped.
Were you in the middle of trying that out?
Fox-dono, if you like that magazine
so much, you can have it.
Take it with you to the underworld.
I hope a horse kicks you to death!
My daughter's not ready to fall in love!
I will take this opportunity to eat cup noodles.
Kokkuri-san, Kokkuri-san, please come out.
My darling, if you're looking for Fox-dono,
perhaps you should just go to the kitchen.
No, summoning Kokkuri-san isn't my goal.
Kokkuri-san is nothing like a fox, and he
does nothing to live up to his back story.
By playing Kokkuri-san, I can make
him seem more like Kokkuri-san.
It's just like you to have such
deep thoughts, my darling.
I admire you. I am sure Fox-dono
will be pleased, as well.
Fox-dono, you should be careful on moonless nights.
Kokkuri-san, Kokkuri-san, please come out.
Sake
You rang?
Change.
An unknown man appeared.
oboete iru kana
覚えているかな
I wonder if you remember
ichiban kanashii toki
一番悲しい時
Your saddest moment
yokei na kotoba wo
余計な言葉を
Needless words
minna sutete kureta
みんな捨ててくれた
Have been cast aside
karappo no ude ni
空っぽの腕に
Wrapped under my arms
sotto mogurikonde
そっと潜り込んで
I've been crouching down
sameta jounetsu
冷めた情熱
The cooled down passion
atatame nagara
温めながら
Starts to warm up again
taisetsu na mono ga
大切なものが
What's precious to me
koko ni hitotsu dake
ここにひとつだけ
There is only one thing
arifureta hibi ni
ありふれた日々に
In these mundane days
shizuka ni nagareru merodi
静かに流れるメロディ
A melody is quietly passing through
issho ni utawanakute mo ii kara
一緒に歌わなくてもいいから
We don't need to sing together
kono mama tenpo ni makasete hoshii
このままテンポに任せて欲しい
I want to leave it to our current tempo
mawaru mawatte
回る　回って
It goes around and around
hikari no naka de
光の中で
Inside the light
mawaru mawatte
回る　回って
It goes around and around
kurikaeshite
繰り返して
Over and over again
Please leave.
Yes                                     No
Yes.
I don't have anywhere to go.
I can't quit drinking and gambling.
I'm unemployed, and my wife and child left me.
I have nowhere left to go back to.
I'm homeless.
Miss, you won't throw me out
into the cold, will you?
Ichimatsu was certain.
At this rate, she'd end up being
haunted by something unpleasant.
Now is the time to use that.
My darling!
Chomp!
Ouch.
The item Kokkuri-san gave
me to drive off my enemies.
It was a personal safety alarm.
Take that.
There's no point if you're not
running away while it's ringing.
Score! I got a bed and food!
She was haunted.
Kohina, you shouldn't play with the personal saf-
Ack! The old tanuki guy!
What are you doing here?
Hey.
Next Episode
Haunting 4              The One on My Mind is Into Sci-Fi!
This Week's Fluff: Smith-kun
What? Seriously?
It's finally a dog! Doggie, doggie!
You rang?
No one was calling you!