Because Kokkuri-san isn't living
up to his back story at all,
I played Kokkuri-san to make him
seem more like Kokkuri-san,
but I accidentally summoned a strange man.
What a nuisance.
You're the old tanuki!
What are you doing here?
All right. I got a housekeeper.
hanchahan isshohan
半チャーハン 一升半
Half fried rice! Half a bushel!
say say
シェイシェイ
Say, say!
yeah yeah
いえーいえー
Yeah, yeah!
gugure! kukure! gugure
繰繰れ！繰繰れ！繰繰れ！
Gugure! Kukure! Gugure!
rereru rerure LOVE★
れれる　れるれー LOVE★
Rereru rerure LOVE★
hi fu mi ah
ひーふーみー 鳴呼
One, two, three, ah!
oh yeah get down boogie
おーいえー　げっだーん　ぶーーぎーー
Oh yeah get down boogie
dance dance dance
だんす　だんす　だんす
Dance, dance, dance
kokon touzai shinkyuu you hou
古今東西　新旧洋邦
All ages past and present, here and across the ocean
ryouri ga dekiru otoko wa moterunda!
料理ができる　男はモテるんだー !
The men should be able to cook!
de? sorede?
で？それで？
And? What of it?
souji mo kanpeki! sentaku mo kanpeki!
掃除も完璧! 洗濯も完璧
Perfect cleaning! Perfect laundry!
airon mo osaihou mo
アイロンも お裁縫も
Ironing and sewing too
ooi shouchu to tako wa sa
おーい焼酎とたこわさー
Hey, get the alcohol and snacks!
jichikai ni mo deterundaze?
自治会にも出てるんだぜ?
How about joining the neighbourhood council too?
go kinjo tsukiai perfect
ご近所付き合いパーフェクト
My relationship with our neighbours is perfect
ha ha
はっは
nanoni nande tei hyouka!
なのに なんで低評価!
And yet why aren't I appreciated?!
hatarake subete wa waga kimi no tame ni
はたらけ全てはわが君のために
Work! It's all for my darling!
subete wa ore no niito seikatsu no tame ni
全ては俺のニート生活のために
It's all for my life as a NEET!
kao wa ii hou darou
顔はいい方だろ
My face looks good, right?
zannen
残念!
Too bad!
kirei na kamishitsu darou
きれいな髪質だろ
My hair is beautiful, right?
shiruga!
白髪!
It's grey!
suiji sentaku wa makasero
炊事洗濯はまかせろ
You can leave the cooking and cleaning to me
okan!
おかん!
Mother!
kamenokou yori toshinokou daro!!
亀の甲より年の功だろ ! !
The older the wiser, right?!
gakugaku iwasezu ni utatte kudasai
ガクガク言わずに歌ってください
Please sing without being outspoken
hai! hai! hai! hai!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
kemo kemo kemo kemoke
ケモケモケモ けもけもけ
ossan nii-san nee-san minasama rasshai!
おっさんにーさんねーさんみなさまらっしゃい！
Old man, brother, sister, everybody come on!
chintonshan! binchoutan!
ちんとんしゃん！びんちょうたん！
tonshan
とんしゃん！
choutan!
ちょうたん！
tarira tarirarira dance! dance! dance!
タリラタリラリラ　ダンス！ダンス！ダンス！
yoisho!
よいしょ！
Heave-ho!
kemo kemo kemo kemo kemoke
ケモケモケモ　けもけもけ
kokuri kokuri burning heart
コクリコクリ　バーニングハート
hanchahan isshohan
半チャーハン 一升半
Half fried rice! Half a bushel!
say say
シェイシェイ
Say, say!
yeah yeah
いえーいえー
Yeah, yeah!
gugure! kukure! gugure!
繰繰れ！繰繰れ！繰繰れ！
Gugure! Kukure! Gugure!
rereru rerure LOVE★
れれる　れるれー LOVE★
Rereru rerure LOVE★
Doki Fansubs | http://doki.co | http://anidex.moe
Haunting 4
"The One on My Mind is Into Sci-Fi!"
Leave!
Go back to Shikoku, you tanuki geezer!
Don't be so cold, old friend.
Shut up! Get out!
Kokkuri-san, is he your friend?
That's right.
Don't insult me! I just can't get rid of him!
This is the tanuki ghost, Shigaraki.
He's a parasitic piece of scum.
You really hate me, don't you?
We used to be roommates.
I like you, you know.
You'd clean the place,
and your cooking was delicious.
Life was so easy.
This is what he's like!
You lived with that old
man and took care of him?
I didn't do it because I enjoyed it!
A really long time ago...
When I lived in a tenement,
he was my neighbour.
It's that neighbour again...
He'd leave for long periods at a time,
inviting bug infestations.
I had no choice but to clean it myself, and then...
Hey! I connected our rooms so
you can clean my place anytime.
He destroyed the wall,
forcing us to become roommates.
I won't let you live with us!
I won't allow anyone else to haunt Kohina!
This place is teeming with animal spirits!
Are you trying to turn Kohina into a zoologist?
If that's how you're going to be,
let's gamble on it, fox.
We'll flip a coin. If it comes up heads, I stay.
Tails, I leave.
How about it?
I bet that coin has heads on both sides.
Yeah, it does.
Okay, here we go.
Which is it?
Don't flip it!
There's no point!
No! I've already decided to live here, so there!
Don't "so there" me!
You're not even trying to trick me anymore!
Get out of here!
Fine, then. I won't use the fake coin.
I'll roll a 4-5-6 die. If it comes
up four, five, or six, I win.
Sound good?
It does not!
There's nothing "good" about it!
I know the faces only have four,
five, and six written on them!
I thought I'd finally found a good home...
A hereditary witch household
haunted by a fox and a dog.
I'm possessed by everything but fortune.
A hereditary witch household?
A hereditary witch household is a family
that employs the ghosts of animals.
As a rule, the ghosts pass
from mother to daughter.
Usually they're haunted by Osaki foxes,
pipe foxes, or other similar spirits.
Hereditary witch households
are envied and feared for
their ability to steal happiness from others.
Starting with you, your family
is now haunted by a dog ghost.
Got it?
Please explain that again in Japanese.
That was in Japanese.
I was haunting another house
with a Tomako tanuki,
but the family fell into ruin.
I'll bet it was you who ruined them.
Won't you at least let me stay
until I find my next family?
Anyone who ruins families isn't welcome here.
I'm offended that you'd think I ruined them.
I always worked hard to bring them riches.
To do that...
I bet everything they had on the horses!
Get out of here, you alcoholic gambling addict!
Hey, I just thought I'd double their money for them.
Stare.
Little girl, if you let me stay, I'll give you this.
Hey!
54 cup noodles!
"1 Cup Noodle = 170 Yen (tax included)"
That's incredible. She's been sulking for three days.
Apologize! Apologize to her!
Okay, okay.
Sorry about that, little girl.
I did that because I don't have any money.
Will this make you forgive me?
Whirr, click. Cup noodles.
Here. Eat some cup noodles and calm down.
I will never forgive that tanuki.
Well, he is a tanuki, so he likes to trick humans.
You shouldn't involve yourself with him.
Fluff, fluff.
If the tanuki man becomes an animal,
the soothing effect might cancel out my rage.
Glug, glug, glug.
Old man.
Yeah?
Can you become an animal?
Of course. What? You wanna see me do it?
Kids sure like animals.
Okay, I'll show you.
There you go.
It wasn't cute.
Come on, you can pet me.
What's wrong?
I prefer the human form, after all.
What?
You prefer a humanoid tanuki?
I did not make such a disgusting request.
Gross.
Run, run.
Don't be shy!
I'll play with you!
Run, run.
Stop that!
Ow...
That hurt! What was that for, fox?
Don't do weird things to Kohina!
Oh, I forgot. Can you lend me some money?
I'll pay you back double.
I don't have any money to lend
to a damn NEET with no income.
Hey, watch your mouth.
Is everyone who's unemployed a NEET?
Guys who can't work even if
they want to are not NEETs!
You... want to work?
What? Of course not.
What are you talking about?
Y-You should watch your own mouth!
You still haven't returned the
money I lent you ages ago!
It was two months' income!
What? Boo, boo.
Pay me back double right now.
Will you lend me money if I give it back?
If you can pay me in cash right now.
Here.
What?
He returned double of 100 yen.
At least convert it to its current value...
My 100 yen from the Meiji Era...
I'm borrowing this.
At the time, 100 yen was a
considerable amount of money.
Damn it. What does he plan to
spend my precious savings on?
I saved that money little by little,
browsing through the sales every day.
I'll go see what he spends it on.
The moment he wastes it on something
stupid, I'll scorch him, wallet and all.
Hey.
Here, I brought candy.
Share it around.
An orphanage?
What is he doing here?
We love you.
Pick me up!
What's going on? What is he doing?
I don't believe this. He seems
like a really good person.
Have you kids been good?
Yeah!
Have you been listening to your teachers?
Why is the old tanuki being so heart-warming?
No way. I'm scared.
Stare.
I brought this month's donation.
Thank you for all your help.
Pick me up!
Okay, here we go.
Up you go.
You're a cute one.
Maybe in ten years, I'll take you to a movie.
Oh, are you a guest?
Um, is he always like that?
Yes. He makes a donation every month.
It helps us a great deal.
We wouldn't be able to keep the
orphanage open without Shigaraki-san.
I don't believe this.
It makes me feel like I really shouldn't burn him.
He's gone from being a NEET
scumbag to a super volunteer.
Does the tanuki man like
taking care of people, too?
Kamakura Friends Orphanage
Shigaraki-san brought the children
here when they had nowhere to go.
That's why they're all so attached to him.
He's truly a good person.
Come back soon, mister.
Bye-bye, mister.
Yeah, see you later.
What, you followed me?
Yeah.
You two love me so much that you're stalking me?
Come here and I'll give you a hug.
Really, you guys are hopeless.
I'll strangle you to death.
Tanuki man, you pretend to be a worthless
bum, but you're actually a good person.
I'm surprised.
Don't get the wrong idea. That's not how it is.
I pretend to be a good person as part of my job.
Your job?
Yeah.
My job is to trick humans.
Since I'm naturally bad, pretending to be good
counts as tricking them, so it makes my job easy.
You are trying to hide your embarrassment.
If that's what you think,
you've already been deceived.
I'm not a good person.
After all,
those kids are the only ones
left of the families I haunted.
It's heartbreaking.
Are you the root of all evil?!
He's scum.
As it turns out, scum is scum.
And so the tanuki man joined their group.
I'm going now.
Okay. Watch out for cars.
What's wrong?
I was just wondering if Kohina
has any friends at school.
Maybe I'll go check on her in secret.
You worry too much, fox.
You'll go bald.
I won't go bald!
I'll always be fluffy!
My Ri*P hair tonic will protect me!
The little girl is fine.
Even being bullied wouldn't faze her.
Bullying is bad!
I'm gonna go check on her!
Okay. I need to disguise myself
so I can fit in at her school.
Well? How do I look?
That uniform isn't fitting in with you.
But kids these days grow up so fast.
Maybe there's a boy the little girl is interested in.
Whoops, can't stand around here.
I'm off to make my rounds.
Th-There's no way my Kohina
is interested in any boys...
Guardians have a responsibility to make
sure their children don't get hurt.
And if there's a boy she's interested
in, I need to check him out.
My intentions are not impure at all.
It's weird to call yourself a doll.
Yeah, it's creepy.
Hey, she'll hear you.
Shall I turn you into
socially-disconnected dolls?
What is she doing?
She had already been acknowledged
as disconnected from society.
Pachinko
Homeroom
Okay, pair up with whoever you like.
Okay.
There's three of us. One will be left over.
What should we do?
Teacher! Can the three of us work together?
I guess it can't be helped. Sure.
Ichimatsu, are you by yourself again?
Kohina!
Why are you looking at Ichimatsu?
Look. The doll on her backpack is cute.
Hey, you're right. I wonder where she got it.
Inugami's even stalking her inside the classroom.
He looks so natural there, I didn't even notice.
Kohina.
Kokkuri-san, what is it?
Are you stalking me?
You'll only cause trouble by coming to my school.
No! I'm just, um, observing your class.
Good grief. You're such a nuisance, Fox-dono.
You're one to talk.
By the way, Kohina, are there
any b-boys you're interested in?
Yes.
D-D-Do you... l-l-like him?
Are you in l-l-love with him?
Dolls do not love. I am only interested.
I always find myself watching him.
Isn't that...
...love?
Who is he?!
Tell me who my target is.
Demon Mother-in-Law
He is the intelligent-looking slim boy
over there with the bright eyes.
I'll find the flaws in that pretty boy.
That's him.
That's a bipedal sentient life form
that reeks of science fiction.
He is an extraterrestrial being.
He's Yamamoto-kun.
Damn it, I let my guard down!
I wasn't expecting an alien to appear!
I thought this was a Japanese fantasy setting!
Yamamoto-kun is a perfectly ordinary boy.
He just looks a bit like a little grey man.
Because he resembles one,
I can't stop looking at him.
No, he more than resembles one.
He's obviously an alien.
You must not judge people by appearances.
He is an Earthling on the inside.
Earth...
Everyone likes Yamamoto-kun
because he's so nice.
The other day, when I tripped in
the hallway, he reached out to me...
E.T.
Then he left without helping me up.
I saw that scene in a movie a long time ago.
And he didn't help you up?
He's so mysterious.
Even his actions are super alien.
He fits in with the class too well to be an alien.
Just the other day...
Yamamoto, are you going
home? You want a ride?
Senpai?
I think I've seen that scene in a movie, too...
A clearly happy boy who rides home in his
friend's bicycle basket can't be an alien.
Aren't there other things you should be noticing?
Hey, you're not bad.
For real?
Anyway, that new game is seriously hard.
The enemy monsters cheat too much.
Why is everyone interacting
with the alien normally?
He's not an alien. He's Yamamoto-kun.
Once you hear his extremely human introduction,
you won't be able to think
of him as an alien anymore.
I'll introduce you to Yamamoto-kun.
Seriously?
Yamamoto-kun.
This is Kokkuri-san.
Hello.
Yamamoto is an Earthling.
E.T.
Earthlings don't call themselves Earthlings!
I'm supposed to believe that introduction?
You're too suspicious of him.
Crap, I forgot my homework!
But why does everyone like him and not you?
Yamamoto-kun, can I see your notes?
He's very popular because he's
good at taking care of people.
No way. Right, Yamamoto-kun?
I know, I know. Please, Yamamoto-kun?
If you keep watching him, you'll
understand why people like him.
He's a good older brother who looks after his
younger sister in place of his working parents.
His younger sister?!
Sibling Love
His popularity is understandable.
Why isn't everyone afraid
of him after seeing that?
Sibling Love
Were you waiting for me?
Yeah. Shall we go?
You waited for her on school grounds?
You're quite the lolicon, aren't y—
What are you doing?
Sometimes Yamamoto-kun's
parents come to pick him up.
His family?
That definitely isn't his family!
They're the guys who take
away aliens to dissect them!
The next time Yamamoto-kun returned
to school was one month later.
oboete iru kana
覚えているかな
I wonder if you remember
ichiban kanashii toki
一番悲しい時
Your saddest moment
yokei na kotoba wo
余計な言葉を
Needless words
minna sutete kureta
みんな捨ててくれた
Have been cast aside
karappo no ude ni
空っぽの腕に
Wrapped under my arms
sotto mogurikonde
そっと潜り込んで
I've been crouching down
sameta jounetsu
冷めた情熱
The cooled down passion
atatame nagara
温めながら
Starts to warm up again
taisetsu na mono ga
大切なものが
What's precious to me
koko ni hitotsu dake
ここにひとつだけ
There is only one thing
arifureta hibi ni
ありふれた日々に
In these mundane days
shizuka ni nagareru merodi
静かに流れるメロディ
A melody is quietly passing through
issho ni utawanakute mo ii kara
一緒に歌わなくてもいいから
We don't need to sing together
kono mama tenpo ni makasete hoshii
このままテンポに任せて欲しい
I want to leave it to our current tempo
mawaru mawatte
回る　回って
It goes around and around
hikari no naka de
光の中で
Inside the light
mawaru mawatte
回る　回って
It goes around and around
kurikaeshite
繰り返して
Over and over again
Next Time
Haunting 5             The Flowers on the Desk are a Message!
This Week's Fluff: Tin-kun
What's this? It looks so fluffy and cuddly and soft!
Why? If you're gonna use a rabbit, use a female.
You can tell a rabbit's gender at a glance?