Actually, Kokkuri-san has a certain weakness.
That is...
To be honest, when it comes to PCs, the internet or phones,
I don't really know how they work, so they scare me.
You're just a geezer left behind the times.
Yeah, sure, you modern day girl!
You've always been bad with stuff like that, haven't you?
Kokkuri-san, it'd be better if you keep up with the times a bit more.
He doesn't even know how to record something on tv.
Hey, hey.
Please record this.
Don't treat me like a fool!
If I get serious, even I can record something!
You wanna see how I record something with G-Code?!
You wanna see?!
G-Code is long gone.
There's no VHS in this house.
Ugh, seriously?!
Of course, Kokkuri-san doesn't know how to wire a tv either.
I'm bad with new devices.
So bad that I break out in hives.
Yes.
It must be hard for you.
By the way, check out my new smartphone, it's the latest gen!
Don't suddenly shove it in my face!
It's fine, it's fine!
Here, here! Feel free to touch it!
In order to help Kokkuri-san overcome his weakness,
she decided to surround him with smartphones.
Huh?! No way!
It'll be okay if you get used to them.
He died.
Kokkuri-san couldn't keep up with the quickly evolving civilisation.
But even though he is like that,
New Rice Cooker Model
he makes sure to buy new home appliances after some years of use.
It is due to a bad experience, when an appliance he had been using for way too long burnt his tail,
and because he is aware that switching to more recent eco appliances is economically advantageous.
No, it will still do!
The refrigerator is still fine
But in the end, Kokkuri-san still is bad with new devices.
"Kokkuri-san's Fear of the Digital"