Have you ever played the Kokkuri-san
divination game with someone?
Players summon a fox ghost to
answer questions by moving the coin
their index fingers are touching.
Is Kokkuri-san simply a children's game,
or is it a form of necromancy?
The truth is unclear.
Yes
No
However, you must never play this game alone.
If you play it alone...
Kokkuri-san, Kokkuri-san, please come out.
You summoned me by yourself?
I guess you wish to be haunted.
You called?
Kokkuri-san, Kokkuri-san,
who is that suspicious man?
Huh? What's your problem?
Don't lock the door.
You're the one who summoned me.
Don't lock the door on me.
"Fox Ghost Kokkuri-san"
Please don't break into my house
by breaking a window, ghost.
I was just being polite when
I asked you to come out.
"Ichimatsu Kohina"
I didn't really want you to show up.
Please leave.
I came all the way here,
and you say you didn't call me?
Please leave money to repair
the window, then leave.
I'm not leaving after coming all this way!
Please leave.
No way!
Maybe I'll haunt you...
Sign: Salt
If you won't leave, I'll drive you away with salt.
Little girl, you can't drive me
away with ordinary kitchen sa-
Begone, evil spirit.
This is the power of salt.
Her physical attack was effective.
How dare you, you little brat?!
Please don't abuse me.
Violence only breeds sadness.
You're one to talk!
Look, you do understand
that I'm Kokkuri-san, don't you?
People are usually more frightened of me.
Nothing hurts me more than
your lack of reaction.
Can't you at least pretend to be shaken?
I am a doll without a heart,
so I do not get frightened.
I do not get "shaken."
I, Ichimatsu Kohina, am a doll.
A doll... a doll... a doll...
Doll... doll...
She's emotionally detached!
Dolls are unaffected by the
uncomfortable stares of others.
She's mentally strong and
emotionally detached!
I am a living doll born of
state-of-the-art biotechnology.
I do not waste energy on anger or joy.
Dolls always operate in an
environmentally friendly manner.
Friendly manner... friendly manner...
Manner... manner...
You don't have any friends, do you?
How did you know?
But dolls are not shaken by a lack of friends.
She's being defiant.
Sufficient time has passed.
Fox Udon
This is my dinner!
Is this stuff all you ever eat?
Cup noodles are a doll's primary source of fuel.
This is unforgivable.
A growing girl shouldn't be eating
this junk!
I'll make you three meals a day,
using 50 different ingredients!
Three meals a day!
50 Ingredients!!
You should have a responsible adult by your side!
Please leave.
Give me a minute!
Kokkuri-san felt he couldn't abandon the
lonely little girl who called herself a doll.
I'm back!
Three meals a day and
50 different ingredients!
Repeat after me!
I prefer cup noodles...
Three meals a day and
50 different ingredients!
50 different ingredients?
I can't hear you!
Three meals a day and
50 different ingredients!
What do you think?
Doesn't it look good?
But I prefer junk food...
Shut up and eat.
I made a lot of food.
Isn't your family home yet?
I live alone, so no one is coming home.
What?
I haven't eaten a meal with
someone else in a very long time.
Don't you feel lonely by yourself?
Dolls feel nothing.
More specifically, I always get the feeling
there's something else in the house,
Ha Ha
Thump Thump
Step     Step     Step
so I never really feel alone.
That's even more heartbreaking!
And you guys! Stop that racket!
Quit haunting this place!
In this manner, Kokkuri-san began his
haunting of the little girl-doll.
Kokkuri-san, Kokkuri-san, please come out.
Don't summon me while I'm in the shower.
What's wrong? Are you hungry?
Do you have a question?
Why aren't you saying anything?
Is it a delicate question?
Oh, perhaps...
you wanted to take a bath with me?
My answer is "Yes."
Hello. Police?
Huh? Wait...
What?
What's going on?
Hey.
Hey. Hey.
Kokkuri-san was forcibly removed.
Seriously, hey.
What?
Hey.
Salt
I'm back!
Thank you for your service.
Please return to the other world now.
No way! I'm going to keep haunting you!
Potato Starch
Don't try to thicken me up!
Don't be heartless and tell me to leave!
I do not have a heart.
I am a doll.
I am a doll, so I do not have a heart.
Dolls are unaffected when
others draw away from them.
Eating lunch alone at school does not unnerve me,
and I am not fazed when my teacher
tells me to pair up with someone I like.
I am not even affected by a half-naked
man with animal ears and a bell.
Are you still upset about that?
I have something important to discuss with you.
Please sit there.
I am sitting.
Enough!
Kokkuri-san has come down to you.
Why don't you ask him a question?
It would be quicker to use Google.
I hate the internet!
You underestimate my powers.
Unlike the internet, I can accurately
answer any and all questions.
Kokkuri-san, Kokkuri-san...
What is the meaning of life?
Is euthanasia a sin?
What is a "crambon"?
What are your measurements?
What colour underwear are you wearing today?
Don't ask questions without answers
and don't sexually harass me!
Then, tell me the answers to my upcoming test.
Certain Victory
Elementary School Drills
Pass Easily
Don't cheat.
You can't answer anything. You're useless.
Your questions are the problem!
The problems with rising sales tax rates and...
No current events.
Then, what will the weather be tomorrow?
That's one I can answer.
Give me a minute.
"Meteorological Agency"... and search.
You're going to Google it?
It has become clear that you are
inferior to a search engine.
Kohina, I didn't do anything, but it broke.
I don't get these hi-tech gadgets...
You're really that bad with technology?
What did you do to it?
This isn't supposed to happen...
There, there. Everyone has
their strengths and weaknesses.
Don't let it get you down.
Kokkuri-san.
Don't make fun of me!
Oh, I know.
I can answer basic questions
about myself right away.
Is there any merit in hearing the answers?
Very well.
Kokkuri-san, Kokkuri-san...
Kokkuri-san, how old are you?
Twenty-five.
Lie                   Truth
This is a lie detector.
"Lie Detector!!"
Lie                   Truth
It can detect lies with 99% accuracy.
"Lie Detector!!"
Lie                   Truth
Kokkuri-san, Kokkuri-san, how old are you?
I have no need to answer that.
Were you lying about your age?
I invoke my right to silence!
Lie                              Truth
Why can't we just say I'm 25?
Kids who ask questions no one wants to
answer don't make any friends. Got it?
Dolls do not need friends.
Don't say such sad things.
Friends are life's treasures.
People grow and learn through
interacting with others.
I see.
You must have lots of friends.
What?
Kokkuri-san, do you have friends?
I-I do.
Please don't include me.
Gulp!
W-We're friends, right? Right?
Is that a threat?
Tangerines
Inu [Dog]
Where are you, my fated one?
I don't want to die alone. I don't want
to die alone. I don't want to die alone...
Kokkuri-san was the one
who was sad and lonely.
Dolls are fine on their own.
Things were good when I was young...
You're not young anymore?
I used to be worshipped at the shrine as a god.
People needed me.
You're not young anymore?
Times changed, and people
stopped believing in me.
When the shrine was demolished,
my home was also-
You're not young anymore?
Shut up.
My real name?
Your name wasn't "Kokkuri-san"
when you were a god, was it?
No, it wasn't.
The names people called me
changed with the times.
Even if you ask which was my
true name, I had so many...
"Ihadsomany"? That's an unusual name.
No!
Ihad Somany?
"Ihad Somany"?
No!
Ihad Somany?
Somany...
"Somany"...
Call me Kokkuri-san!
Somany...
Come to think of it, you used to come
play at my shrine when you were little.
I did?
Non-Sacred Tree
I curse thee, I curse thee, I curse thee...
You were the only one who came
to play at my dilapidated shrine.
It made me happy...
I sometimes watched over you from afar.
When you played Kokkuri-san...
Kokkuri-san, come on.
I figured you must have been calling
me, so I started haunting you.
Don't they call people like you "stalkers"?
Don't you mean "guardians"?
Kokkuri-san might be a dangerous ghost.
Komachi Market
Maybe I'll clean the yard today...
Kohina!
Hey, what's wrong? Are you okay?
Beep.
Internal power low. Switching
to suspended animation mode.
Please replenish energy.
Growl
You're just hungry?
Please replenish energy.
I'd make you ramen anytime.
Ramen is no good because
it's delicious by design.
I find the non-nutritious and cheap
quality of this udon irresistible.
Fox Udon
Viva la artificial additives.
Do you eat properly when I'm not here?
Yes.
To maintain a balanced diet,
I eat a wide variety of cup noodles.
Fox Udon
Oh Noodles
That's not balanced at all!
I told you not to eat unbalanced meals!
I'm confiscating this!
It's not good for you!
I'm confiscating these!
Empty
Hand over the ones you're hiding, too!
You bought way too many of these!
Give me the one you're
hiding behind your back!
I don't have anything.
Kohina!
I'm not doing anything wrong.
Don't kill it! Don't kill my cup noodles!
You junkie!
All of them were disposed of
by returning them to the store.
Empty
My collection... My stock...
Even my limited edition noodles
and the ones they stopped making...
Kohina's shaken. She's shaken...
What?
You're a demon. This is the act of a demon.
I'm sorry. I had no idea they
were so important to you...
I hate you, Kokkuri-san.
What is that?
I found it in the storehouse.
It's the Sword of the Fallen Hero.
Please decide if you would
rather disappear immediately,
or offer your ears and tail as compensation.
Then give me your ears.
Farewell!
I failed to get his ears and tail.
Kokkuri-san actually left.
Kokkuri-san, Kokkuri-san...
Please come out.
No matter how many times she played
Kokkuri-san after that, he never appeared.
I'm sure he'll be back soon.
It's not a problem that Kokkuri-san isn't around.
Good morning!
Good morning.
Did you see what was on TV last night?
Kokkuri-san was the only one
who spoke to Ichimatsu.
Oh Noodles
Kokkuri-san isn't here, so I can
eat all the cup noodles I want.
Oh Noodles
Kokkuri-san still hadn't returned.
It's not a problem at all
that Kokkuri-san isn't around...
At least...
It shouldn't be...
Kokkuri-san, Kokkuri-san...
Why am I crying?
Why don't my cup noodles taste good?
Kokkuri-san, Kokkuri-san, I seem to be broken.
Will I never get to eat your cooking again?
No
I'm back.
I didn't think you'd miss me so much you'd cry.
I'm moved.
So it's true that you should back off a bit
when a direct approach doesn't work.
I went to buy back all your cup
noodles while running away.
I thought losing me would teach you
how important I am to you so that
you'd never tell me to leave again.
What is it?
You look as though you've
been bewitched by a fox.
Were you bewitched?
Did the fox bewitch you?
To make up for it, you can impose
on my kindness all you want.
Come into my arms!
Ow! That hurts!
And so, Kohina beat on
me all night- No, wait!
And so, I decided to haunt Kohina.
Here begins a new life for a somewhat
unusual girl named Kohina and a fox ghost.
From my perspective, it is transient...
only lasting until we part ways.
Please take in this cute doggie and shower him with love.
Until the promise made that day is fulfilled,
I will surely stay by Kohina's side.
Haunting 1
"Doll Girl Meets Kokkuri-san!"
hanchahan isshohan
半チャーハン 一升半
Half fried rice! Half a bushel!
say say
シェイシェイ
Say, say!
yeah yeah
いえーいえー
Yeah, yeah!
gugure! kukure! gugure
繰繰れ！繰繰れ！繰繰れ！
Gugure! Kukure! Gugure!
rereru rerure LOVE★
れれる　れるれー LOVE★
Rereru rerure LOVE★
hi fu mi ah
ひーふーみー 鳴呼
One, two, three, ah!
oh yeah get down boogie
おーいえー　げっだーん　ぶーーぎーー
Oh yeah get down boogie
dance dance dance
だんす　だんす　だんす
Dance, dance, dance
kokon touzai shinkyuu you hou
古今東西　新旧洋邦
All ages past and present, here and across the ocean
ryouri ga dekiru otoko wa moterunda!
料理ができる　男はモテるんだー !
The men should be able to cook!
de? sorede?
で？それで？
And? What of it?
souji mo kanpeki! sentaku mo kanpeki!
掃除も完璧! 洗濯も完璧
Perfect cleaning! Perfect laundry!
airon mo osaihou mo
アイロンも お裁縫も
Ironing and sewing too
ooi shouchu to tako wa sa
おーい焼酎とたこわさー
Hey, get the alcohol and snacks!
jichikai ni mo deterundaze?
自治会にも出てるんだぜ?
How about joining the neighbourhood council too?
go kinjo tsukiai perfect
ご近所付き合いパーフェクト
My relationship with our neighbours is perfect
ha ha
はっは
nanoni nande tei hyouka!
なのに なんで低評価!
And yet why aren't I appreciated?!
hatarake subete wa waga kimi no tame ni
はたらけ全てはわが君のために
Work! It's all for my darling!
subete wa ore no niito seikatsu no tame ni
全ては俺のニート生活のために
It's all for my life as a NEET!
kao wa ii hou darou
顔はいい方だろ
My face looks good, right?
zannen
残念!
Too bad!
kirei na kamishitsu darou
きれいな髪質だろ
My hair is beautiful, right?
shiruga!
白髪!
It's grey!
suiji sentaku wa makasero
炊事洗濯はまかせろ
You can leave the cooking and cleaning to me
okan!
おかん!
Mother!
kamenokou yori toshinokou daro!!
亀の甲より年の功だろ ! !
The older the wiser, right?!
gakugaku iwasezu ni utatte kudasai
ガクガク言わずに歌ってください
Please sing without being outspoken
hai! hai! hai! hai!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
kemo kemo kemo kemoke
ケモケモケモ けもけもけ
ossan nii-san nee-san minasama rasshai!
おっさんにーさんねーさんみなさまらっしゃい！
Old man, brother, sister, everybody come on!
chintonshan! binchoutan!
ちんとんしゃん！びんちょうたん！
tonshan
とんしゃん！
choutan!
ちょうたん！
tarira tarirarira dance! dance! dance!
タリラタリラリラ　ダンス！ダンス！ダンス！
yoisho!
よいしょ！
Heave-ho!
kemo kemo kemo kemo kemoke
ケモケモケモ　けもけもけ
kokuri kokuri burning heart
コクリコクリ　バーニングハート
hanchahan isshohan
半チャーハン 一升半
Half fried rice! Half a bushel!
say say
シェイシェイ
Say, say!
yeah yeah
いえーいえー
Yeah, yeah!
gugure! kukure! gugure!
繰繰れ！繰繰れ！繰繰れ！
Gugure! Kukure! Gugure!
rereru rerure LOVE★
れれる　れるれー LOVE★
Rereru rerure LOVE★
Doki Fansubs | http://doki.co | http://anidex.moe
Assuming I live that long...
Next Episode
Haunting 2
A Refreshing Smile is the First Step Towards Becoming a Real Human!
This Week's Fluff: Mop-chan
What a cute cat.
Wait, isn't this the Kokkuri-san preview?
Fluffy, fluffy...